I feel like I've been locked out
Spend my soul in a way I shouldn't have thought out
Hmm a part of my brain was right
I thought that I could win but the chest is fine. Won't you bet on me?
They said I wasn't reasonable. Nothing was debatable with me. I tried to fly
His eyes are just so meek, meek
But I don't, I am so meek, meek
I'm gonna take a destiny to the truth
Right up the last street
And don't tell your lies
And you're adding to me
On the corner with the most peace
Did you know that he was lonely?
Just commuted
I'm about to get food, so I'm going to compute it, so I'm going to give it a rest
All I want is chaos, that is best
I'm gonna take a taxi, see you this full night of the last week
Don't tell your mom, can you die? I can't believe you
I'm so on her with emotions
I'm going to take a taxi to the shore side of the country, and don't play your moth in your head for too long.
You gave me less, you wanted more, but you didn't give me less
You said that you would always back me back, but now I know what to respect
I'm gonna take a picture of you, the first time I've ever flashed you
You don't tell your mom, and you're happy
On the corner with emojis
You know that I am lonely
I stick to this book out of the live stream
And tell your mom to have her dream
On the corner with emojis
You know that I am lonely
shadow band again
bro mute your mic
drop a bass line dirtier than the chest
up up up
ghost is crashing out
smashing rafters like vows
Canada drives
stick and watch cat along
how randos ranting bout
eh I tunes while his playlist
saw cartoons
I have ten thousand more
What the hell is that mess?
So please, some sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep
It's also true.
This happens. Hey, Dougie Doug. I didn't have anything to do with that
Can I help that that somebody named Alexander McQueen porn bombed you that he wasn't even the Alexander McQueen?
Here's a terrible
Who's this guy? Oh, excuse me. Are you the guys from Samans?
Of course
Why are you so cute?
Can I have sex with you?
No
Please
Please so my question is is why do you eat bag and not take
Because one time I asked for fish tacos like eight months ago
I said can someone send me $10 for fish tacos, and then I wouldn't got them right, but and now I'm
What drugs are you on I wish I was on some drugs. I'm on some high on life. Unfortunately just high on life
You just see me. I'm not doing this. Yes, I am. No, you're not. No, you're not. Actually, I'm just high McDonald's coffee. Yeah. Can you send me some fish chocos?
Here, Alex wants to talk to you. He wants to talk to you. Okay.
My question to you is, Alex, you're terrible. Why do you give a fuck? And why do you sit there like a loser with a mask on with a pink piece of shit shirt, which shows your physique? So you must be 120 pounds soaking wet.
So Alex oh Alex
So we can see your board ass
Alex a dog take it off
to be able to
Understand no man does shit like that. That's why shit with the wife decorates the house
Considering a guy that
You dickhead considering nothing
Consider you little fucking wife hung up your little doll behind you
I'm sorry. Didn't you say you want a fucking baggie? Shut the fuck up. Yeah, okay. Oh
It's ghost. It's ghost
Is it ghost? Ghost. It's ghost, yep. Reveal yourself. Person of the mask. I need to see it. Oh, let me tell you
Let me hear his voice for five minutes. I'll tell you exactly what it is. You won't know who it is. It's J-Dog
It's J-Dog. No, it's not J-Dog, bro
It's not J. Joe J. Joe's your friend. This is one of your enemies. Yeah, so
You understand this is fucking uh, the teacher train. This is one of your enemies
Okay, it's okay. That's right
You're fake cop
Yeah, I'm a fake cop. Oh, wow
So you have a fake pfp a pfp. Yeah bitching about me. Yeah
So I'm not then who you hold up that little doll behind your head was it you did you get on the steve ladder?
Or was it your mom or your wife?
Look at his dick look at his dick he boy who at the party city board of masks said I'm gonna talk to psyche and Alex
With his little stupid skeleton behind them
Skeleton in that piece of shit house
What a loser Alex the terrible shot the fuck up you fucking lose it's thing that is by the way
Psychic it is thing that is end of story
It took me less than two minutes that is thing that is
Alexandra may is
Hey, baby
Is that are you mad that you didn't pass the bar?
Think that is are you mad that you get exposed they live with your mom at 60 years old in her townhouse?
Okay, okay, mommy. Where's mommy now? Where's your fucking crippled uncle?
With your little fucking cartoon dickhead you went to Porty City and you have dolls hanging up on your wall
Thing that is get a life. Don't ever turn your head. It's so we can see your bald head again
We just saw your bald head when you turn
Pretend to be a police officer. We just saw your bald head turn to the right again
So I can see your bald head again
Thing that is
haha oh my god yo thing that is I didn't mean to um have alexandra mayors do a
whole fucking like sting on you bro look how he rubs his head you saw he
rubs his head right now that's nothing that is rubs his head
alexa terrible his things that is my peeps the 50 year old canadian loser
hey leave out this thing that is a love
Oh, look at him. That is what you just shaved your head.
Look how fat the terrible is.
That is nothing that is because that's a terrible spot.
Oh my God. You know who that is, bro?
That's that fucking dickhead, Oliver.
Oliver with the tits, with the main tits.
Look how fat that mother of this guy has main tits.
You can see his bra.
Yo, this is Ghost or Oliver, this motherfucker has minted a fucking skeleton hanging on the wall.
Oh my god, it's all of them are peeps
Oh my god, it was mantis. I saw mantis. I did see man. I think it's a woman. You saw those mantis. That's crazy
No man should have man boobs. You should be killed on site if you
Are a man with mantis like that's for girls, bro
If you're asked can't hold the ham and salami down enough
Or workout or at least go jogging or and you know that you have man boobs
You're not a man
Once there's like a nip, like a little fad hanging off your tits, you're not a man, no mola.
Alex, I send this song to Elisa. I was like hoping that she would like it.
You know, she rolled her eyes. She like looked uncomfortable. She was like made this face.
But she's still alive. When the hell did you see Elisa? I thought she was like the support from the planet.
Like that and she didn't like my song. Well, I'm sorry Lisa. I tried to do I try my best with it
But no, nobody likes me anymore. So it's fine
But I still love you. Yeah, you know, you're not popular lately. I'm not the main
Mason don't came up if you have that same shirt on man because I'm gonna freak out
Campo
I don't get how stupid you are or not
Okay, if you can sit here and say hey psyche. Hey psyche. Why does people in the chat talk shit about me?
You can go to fucking TJ max and get a shirt. You don't even have to leave your house there
So you go to Amazon calm and they have like a 20 pack for five hours Haynes t-shirts
Anything why do you wear that same shirt every fucking time you came up?
They see your little comfy blanket Mason. I'm done. I'm not gonna let this shit slide no more. I need an answer
Are you demented are you sick?
You wash it like how often do you wear it? When do you wash it? Do you have 30 of them? Is it the same shirt?
I need answers motherfucker
Yeah, it's the same shirt it's the same shirt so you take it off every night you put it
Because you sweat as well every day, you know that as a human your glands sway so use your armpits
They smell so once you wear a shirt once it's dirty
You're supposed to wear a shirt one time underwear socks one time
Take them off and then they're dirty. They go in the hamper
You don't wear things twice
Right, then you go to the laundry and wash them, bro. If you wear something twice, you're nasty
But you wear that shirt every fucking time you came up
Yeah, I've been wearing it like different times do you shower
Not that much not that much that's disgusting
What does that mean you're supposed to shower two times a day as well
What do you mean not that much?
You don't shower you don't wash your dick your balls
You know you pee every day right you pee every day at least a few times a day and I'm sure you shit
So your asshole and your dick get dirty dick in a stand. That's disgusting. You have to clean that daily
That's why that's why you have a shower in your home to clean your fucking dirty ass and pee pee
So you say not that much
I don't really you know what disgusting that is my man, and you're a drummer. I
Just don't have a like time in like up. You don't have time to shower
Yeah, you have time to sit here with psyche for hours you obviously have time to shower a
Shower it can be five minutes, but jump in washable shampoo boom boom boom, you know
, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man,
no body
you
who watches your sock and underwear how often do you clean like your sheets on your bed
who makes your bed
who cooks you breakfast
I'm the one who does it
you do everything
yeah I eat my food and stuff like that
you eat your food you eat your food
okay cool who cooks it for you though
Shut the fuck up Mason you piece of shit. You're fucking retarded. It's acting put bro. You're the biggest show up here
so
God is on to you. God is right
You're a fucking moron whoever believes that this guy is like Mason the drummer should jump over bridge right now
This is the biggest show up here
Okay, so Mason shut the fuck up get out of my face. I'm done with you
Oh, also, how do you say it, Uma, Uma, Uma, what was that first time?
Yeah, that's what I mean, the Uma, I don't know.
That was, yeah, because it's been free.
There's one that they did designate a comment, but still it's unclear.
And now we got this third one coming.
I don't think that it's a comment.
I think that it's a share.
That's what I think
Interesting as well is that we're other keys since it is like a like an object in the sky
I was able to go and look at my
Astrology and I was able to find that
That body that that space body and see where it was when we were born see it
So we so we have that actual thing in our science. So I know yours. I know mine
I'm gonna do a remix of the song you did before Alex. Oh my song? Yeah, here's a remix. Oh
Wow, that was it. I think that was it. I mean, I feel like I was just programmed or something. What was that?
I
Didn't really hear the song
There's nothing to cook. There's nothing to cook Jamie
The guy doesn't change his shirt. What what what can I cook that he hasn't cooked himself?
Hot dogs and shove it down your fucking throat one by one when you docks your fucking wife
You came up here and you fronted your own fucking wife. You fucking ice cream chucker hot dog fucking
slender lure
She's talking about J-dog
Psych
I got a fucking job Mike. This bitch is fucking making me irate. I'ma turn dyke if I got a chill with psych
Fuck you at man. I will go dyke if I stay on the panel for another motherfucking minute
Got shit to do hallelujah. Yo, shout out to chat. Yo, and let me tell y'all saying
Bronsberg doesn't know how to fucking be lit. I'm always lit. He's quitting you son whether beta was
Wait, wait a white person and this guy's black
And she did a good job at fucking China battle with this like guy with a bird emoji
And she took the W. Yeah
You lost though. I did
Well, let's play it. Let's play it again, bro. We haven't heard it 10,000 times
Listen, why are you being quiet Mason? He's crying
psyche yeah
Psychic shut up asshole dickhead go to Macy's get Amazon up
One sure boy back fight back fight back with them this guy's one shirt, bro
There's not a fight back my man, please don't tell him to fight back
Hey Alice is a dick. I'm sorry Mason. I'm sorry
Psyche, what's wrong with me wearing the same shirt though? Nothing's wrong with it. Nothing's wrong. It is Alice being a dick
So I can I can wear what I want. No, look Psyche, I can wear what I want to wear. That's what I'm trying to say.
I know you can't. Yeah
He's a dick
Psyche, somebody can't tell me like
Like you somebody can't tell me like what to wear and stuff like that. I can wear like what I feel like we're
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have started this stream. I'm sorry. I'm gonna go away
Mason, I love you. Okay
So I see why you
It's like why are you gonna leave though? You can't stay up here
I'm sad. I'm too sad to like stay on
Why are you too sad though? What happened?
It's just like everyone hates me and like I'm having fun. I'm your friend though. It's like you. I'm your friend though. I know you are
Thank you for being my friend. Thank you. So I mean, there's no reason to leave though
It's like you have to wait so I'm actually here. I'll stay if per page comes here
I'll stay seven talk to her in like months. Well, what about me though?
I get that you think I'm cool. I do think you're cool. You I want you to say too. You're here already
Yeah, but if you you said if somebody doesn't come you're gonna leave even if I'm still here
Well, I'll say I'll say I'll say I'll say as long as you see
Okay
Okay, are you good Mason? I'm sorry. I missed you. Yeah, I'm just making sure but it's like you should let somebody do that to me
Though what I'm on here. I know I'm sorry. Hey Alex Alex if you come back here and pick on Mason again
I'm gonna fuck your ass
That good Mesa
Yeah, okay. Just like it's okay. Yeah, that's good. Okay. She heard it. You heard it here live
What do you have to say about that Alex?
Alexander McQueen
That's not gonna help you
Cole is you're gonna
Yeah, okay, you stay backstage
so I can why would you let him back on though if that's what he's gonna say and stuff like
He's just gonna say negative stuff man. No, he wants to fuck my ass if I fuck with Mason
So fuck you Mason. Fuck you. Come on. So I could get the low, baby
Mason you know don't don't try me with a good time. I mean like that wasn't a good friend
If he likes that means he likes that it's not even a threat to exactly Mason
He's trying me with a good time
Like I'm just here just to chill man. I'm just here just to hang out. I don't want any problem Alex Alexander
He's just here to chill. We're all here to chill dick. It should be nice if he changed the shirt once in a millennium
That's all but let's bring page up
You come back if you page page came in and she's like what the fuck if she's left. She was like never mind
I'm sorry page page. I love you
I call page on the golf course with no shoes on and then the bottom of he would dirty and I screen shot at it
I'm crazy
Mason shut the fuck up we're trying to get page up here
You see you like Alex Mason
What's like yeah, I can only be here if you're gonna just like be on because I can't be here
What's like it's kind of hard to be here what somebody else is trying to be like negative
Like he's saying stuff that's not like positive though. It has to be negative though. I know is he terrible. He's terrible first
he's terrible but psyche why would you i don't get it psyche why would you let him back though if
that's all he's gonna do he's you know i saw alex ones he was bending over um picking up something
is in it
Hey
Alex weird dude, why'd you screenshot my feet you creep?
Alex explain the page
Because because you're too perfect and pretty so I I caught it and I'm like she she's not she's not
Perfect. She her feet are dirty
I screen shot it you you took your little sandal off my moon you were going on the golf like escapade everyday golfing
One day you took your sandals off you in the spoon boom shorts you in the spoon shorts
And I'm like oh my god look at her ass like her legs like well, she's hot
You know you were showing it and then you ran to like the car and then and then you double the bottom of your feet
We're really dirty, and I just screen shot in that ship
As ammunition one day if you come at me, I'm gonna just pop it up. Oh, I'm just gonna throw it up there
So be careful. I got ammo. I'm always watching and I'll catch the crazy as shit
And when you least expect it, I'll pop it up. They go really dirty feet go plaque
Super dirty, but I mean you're walking around grass
Well, maybe I'm like, I don't know they shouldn't be that dirty
Thinking like are they dirty from her home?
Miss you too, so what what's every while you cool cats been up to you also mason you ask a lot of questions bro
Don't do that to me
Mason you have a question
So like you wanted I ever asked her it's like I never even asked her a question before ask her one now
No, so I don't listen to her no like you don't listen to her she's saying the wrong stuff man
No, no, no, no, I'm gonna listen to Paige because Paige knows shit Paige knows shit. So I'm gonna always trust her
Yeah, but thank you. No, no, thank you. I'm more honest and calm down. I got I accomplished what I wanted your shits and to not relax
So I key I was I'm being more honest than she's ever been. Okay, so
She doesn't even know me either though, so I see the same thing
This is Mason that you're out. You're both awesome people. I love you guys. Hi Mason
I just don't want any of the stupid stuff happening. Yeah. Bye Mason. All right
Every time I see lobster I think a page
Also weird, but all right
30 feet in lobster
Oh my god, no, that's a day, baby
I love you guys eat so much.
What's wrong, Mason?
I'm just making sure, like, because the response came here because I was coming to talk to you,
so I got in here to talk about other stuff.
That's the thing about a paddle, Mason, is there's lots of people on it, not just sight.
Exactly.
You can't just tell sight to take people off because they'll be mean to you.
Mason, you know you're gonna get a big big set of balls. Yeah, I've had
Psyche I just wanted to come see you though. I came on here because you're my friend and stuff. It's okay
No, we're in stuff
Brandon stuff. What stuff?
You went to the link somewhere. I got you. I got you girl. Oh god
She's jealous. You know, you know, this is what she's jealous summer is this whole love of me that she can't stand that mean page
I'll be alone. She's jealous now. She has to come up
summer time in the city
Fuck that
I love her. Shut up, I love her.
But her tits are huge. I like tits, like normal tits.
Like, you know, human tits. I don't even know, 30 pound watermelons, fucking
psycho.
Just because I don't agree with
Really awesome, so you really need to watch what you're like be chill out. Okay dude like seriously
Yeah, it is not that serious and you don't need to take three minutes of the show to talk about
What you don't want problems. You don't want problems stop doing the shit you're doing
Page is awesome and we love her so and she always
You could never
Can you throw change a shirt in there?
throughout
So back off mason
Don't tell me what to do
No, I will tell you what I will tell you. I will tell you what to do. What are you gonna do?
Split my throat like you so goddy
You ain't gonna do shit in a boy, I'll fuck you up, I'll fuck you up, you slow motherfuckers.
You don't say that, you don't say that Mason.
Fuck you Mason.
You slow motherfucker.
Oh, I know who that dickhead is, the fucking dude Alex is terrible, that's that fucking freak red devil from Florida.
That's that fat fuck.
You look like I say that guy I say you either red double or I say
Okay
I say
Say look I say doesn't have the tattoo psych wake up
Wow, I say it doesn't have that tattoo on his chest my man. What is it? What is it? That's a BKG
No, you know what it is. That's that red devil fat fuck
The reason that it's a cool
Sikey psyche, how could you let somebody talk to me like that? Tell me what to do
Mason Mason shut the fuck up
How old are you Mason?
Thank you. Why do you let people talk to me that way? Shut the fuck up. What is he your mom?
How old is this guy?
Change your shirt asshole and shut the fuck up
Oh my gosh, okay guys, we're getting off the rails.
Mason, it's okay.
Mason, you feel like hanging out?
You can hang out, but it's gonna be brutal.
Or Alex, the terrible will come get you.
Well, Miss Baby Chakes, then you come up here.
If you think I only mess with weak people
and you ain't weak, then bring your eyes on
up here on this panel.
Whoever asked the terrible is put the shirt back on bro. That's too much fat. You're too fat to be smelling bad, bro
Let's say Shannon is that the woman Shannon in the mask
Mason's threatened to beat people up and I don't have Goddy and y'all up here
Fill us a pipe away cuz somebody's giving a push back fuck that shit
Mason did you want to live somebody?
Remember when he threatened to unalive a Goddy
Mason and he threatened to just threatened to beat me up
So I can I like I can only talk to you. I don't want to talk to the other people are making me mad
You get mad you threatened me you said you're gonna beat me up cuz I told you to be nice to page
That's why I can't talk with the people wonder being like this
Well, then don't get on don't get on the public panel. Oh calm your class
Mason's a show got calm your tits Mason. Oh
Alex left. How are you guys doing tonight?
Good just so I'm like psyche. I was just coming here having a normal time then people want to start stuff
And I don't get it man. Well, they say you're starting to summer because you're not gonna be anybody
No, but she started it
We will tag TV
Mason so I got it so I got it nothing, but just to come here to hang out with you and
Well, you started being mean to Paige for no reason and I told you to chill the fuck out
And then you said are you's gonna beat me up so that I said you was a slow motherfucker. That's pretty much how it went
holler
Okay, Mason is that cool
No, it's like I wasn't looking for any problems man. I told you that okay. It's Mason
It's gonna get crazy tonight. I promise you so what's like you all the times we talk this never happens though
It's all this recent stuff. I think it happens every time. It doesn't happen every time you you threatened on a lab
Goddy on a panel like a week ago
Oh, and it happens
Right. It's every time it happens. What happened?
Stop threatening
Uh-oh. Did you go? Amazing. Come on. No, that was Alex. Okay.
You're amazing.
Sike, Sike, Sike, so what do I do? Like if people talk to me, like, do you agree with it?
So I can't always agree with people saying stuff like, so I'm just trying to be...
I'm in a safety burrito like psych is right now.
Right.
I'm in a burrito.
So like you know the rule me like what I'm always trying to be nice on here like most of the time
I know I get the way I get but I'm saying like, you know
You can understand me when I'm normal and stuff like most of the time when I am
It's okay
So I'll take a deep breath. Hey pages somewhere here or friends. They're friends
Wait, so so psych you're saying you want me to apologize what you want me to do or what do you want me to apologize to summer?
Okay, Summer, I didn't mean anything, but I just I just don't like being talked to you that way. That's why I got that
I understand I understand that but when you sit there and you said you tell more truth and then page
And all this
Let me finish let me finish and you started seeing all this stuff about page and she you don't even know her
She's been around here for a very long time
So right now wait a minute if you start saying things like that then you better expect that someone that loves page
Is gonna jump on panel and tell you to pipe the fuck down
No, I can see what you're saying, but I'm saying like there's no reason for you to go that far the way you did
You could have said in a nice
Now I don't need I don't need to use threatened to beat me up. Once you threatened to beat me up
I don't give a fuck what you're talking about
No, no
I told you not to pick on page, that's what I told you.
Now I said that after you said what you said though, that's why I said what I said.
I don't get the point.
I'd like to speak so I made a joke and I was just bugging you because it's real easy to get your shit in a knot and I was like
Oh, it's my turn to finally, you know do that because I don't come up very often anymore
And then you decided to threaten and then summer didn't like that and neither did well
I mean I didn't really give a shit
But other people didn't like it very much and so now you just say sorry and then we move the fuck on and we have a great time
And that's right. That's that's what I mean
That's that's a good point you're making but I'm just trying to say I wanted to come here to be like, you know
Good with people but then people get all on to me about not changing my shirt. I don't want to hear all that stuff
Well, we didn't say that
Harry Springer time, let's go
Hey, and we have Paige back. Hey, I love you Paige. I love you summer. Yeah, I've been having a weird time
it's like I know you guys are my friends and
I'm thankful for it. I didn't mean anything about you not being like
I mean you could be cool with a page if you you can be cool with whoever you want to be with so I know it's
Has nothing to do with me, but I'm saying yeah, we've known him we've known him a lot longer
So
But psyche I thought we had something going with each other though. That's why I can't
We're friends too, and you know what and it's like it's called sharing Mason. We learned it in grade one in kindergarten
Yeah, we're all friends Mason and said you getting upset you should be like hey page. What's up?
Hey summer like we're all we can all be friends, but you don't have to
I meant, not Paige, I meant Summer, the reason I got that way is because Alexander got me
in a mood I'm not trying to get into right now.
That's why I got that way too.
Yeah, but we didn't do that to you, so you took something out that Alexander did to you
on us, right?
No, I could understand that, but that's why I apologize, it's like you want me to apologize,
so I did.
Thank you, Mason.
I don't know.
We accept your apology.
We were just explaining how it happened, that's it.
No, but summer can you forgive me though if I I mean, I really don't know why I said that yeah, I shouldn't have went that far
Yeah, it's okay. I forgive you
Look Mason roll. Well summer if you don't give me any more chances
Can I at least have one more chance if that's what it is?
Yes, you're gonna have another chance. Just know that if you say something
Yeah, but summer if you don't agree with me like next time then you could just you know, just be done with me if you want
I don't need
We're just having Friday fun. Okay. It's fucking Friday bitches
We're just having fun tonight. I've been through too much stress that relationship and stuff. I just want to have a good time
Okay, it's like psyche. I didn't mean to turn it in a different way. It's out
But you know what? Yeah, it's it's all good Mason. It's just words like we're moving on
Yeah, okay
So fuck you with me and stuff like you know, I know I'm not like perfect and thank you for putting up with me because
I can be a handful. I know so thank you guys
Hey Mason, just just put your lips together and keep them that way for one second. Cool. Thanks bud. So
I don't know what's been going on,
but like I love all of you guys equally
and I'm gonna just say that.
And I don't like drama and you know that.
So, but I'm happy to be here and I really missed you
and I love you too.
Cyker, Rony.
Cyker, Rony, oh, thank you.
And yeah, I know I've been having like issues
with a few people and like people are mad
and it's like, I'm not.
Handling things the best way maybe but uh, but I miss you Paige. I hope you're doing good and
Somewhere I love you. Hope you're doing good. Amesa. I love you. I hope you're doing good
It's like I just want everyone to who's coming on page someone on the
I'm good. I love you, too. I am gonna jump down though because I have a huge event tomorrow
I have to do so
Even the fucking world on a Saturday. Okay. Love you, babe. Thanks for coming up
You too
I hope you have a good night
Okay
Talking cock tomorrow or summer
Always Alex too bad
A-page
Well, hello, handsome. What are you guys having like a slumber party up here? What's going on?
Apparently apparently a good old pillow fight
It's always a pillow fight with me around they said don't give me no bullshit
Well, at least you get fought over that means you're important right important day. I
Love you guys. I love you guys so much
You little avatar thing guys, it's not showing
It's not showing man. It's just a blank. They have good times up here now. It's all videos
Well, it was kind of that before but with like a little bit of tenderness in between and some fucking trivia everyone now
And then with a giggle. Yeah, there's no more giggling. It's just yelling all the time a little bit of tenderness
Tenderness in between and a lot of mason's like yes final comer as much as because it's just too much like you know yelling and
Stuff that each other and too much drama stuff like that
There's a cycle on their covers Mason a lot of yelling. Do you see psyche on their covers? He's on the covies
He's got a little pig. I was gonna give a fucking kiss then Alex. What the fuck dude? We can all psyche shows your piggy
Yes, and he says a little piggy pillow. It's a pig
Get him a fucking
No, he does that one. Oh shit
No, he does dig. I'm surprised. It doesn't have a hole in it. It's the best thing on earth little piggy pillow. Yeah, bro
Come on
Thank you. I saw that six months ago and I lost my mind
Oh god, come on. I know my psycharones, baby
And you wonder why I'm up here fighting for this
He's got a piggy pillow
Paige you got one of those two
Well, I don't have a piggy pillow, but Grace and I have matching little fucking squish mellow things and they can be
Oh, the squish mellows, yeah, so I suppose I kind of do, yeah, but I don't sleep with it
It sits in my closet, and I got to make eye contact with it and shit like it's turned around
Psyche
What's up Mason?
I kind of like normal conversations, you know, that's why it really
Is it this is no one's gonna get this is don't look at the monster psyche. Look at the monster
screenshot that picture
And send it out a master computer and come to calm down with the manure show the other side. That's his ass
Mason you like this
Sikey, what is that man? It's a it's a it's a pink pillow. That's mr. Winky
That's Mr. Wanky, man.
That's how I make the 85 questions at the same time.
So I get supposed to be a pig?
My piggy, yeah.
Poor, that poor pig.
It's my pig yellow.
it's like Piggie Lowe
so it feels good
it's like it feels good
it feels great
it's the cat hot pillow
I love it
oh god yes
don't say my name while you do that
we're all laughing like everybody doesn't have one of those
Paige what do you have
what is it a penguin
I've never seen one of those before
you all got some kind of crazy little pillow
mine is a peregrine falcon
I use it as a knee pillow. I've got a heated blanket and it's like
My favorite thing in the planet. It'll be middle of winter and I'm just sleeping under my little heated blanket and a little ball
Like a cat like a little
No, everyone needs a knee pillow man that needs to hurt right just jamming into each other knee pillows are like
the
Guess what? You know, you know what killed them was the thing behind them
He was acting big and bad until I called out that somebody taped the
Skeleton on the wall and he was like he's right like that just throws your whole game off man
You can't have big and bad with some tape Halloween thing behind you. No, he shouldn't be matching masks for his nipples
the
you look like a sacrifice
put it away you look like a sacrifice
we all have to dress up in matching fucking white togas and he's a sacrifice
oh my god white togas with nothing on the knees page
the time has come on 25
psychokat is behind you man
your cat is behind you man
what's your name?
Santa Mesa
With with the with the feet being clean and dirty
He's sleepy as fuck look at him
He's probably like trying to hold in diarrhea something bro like
Oh
Page you're done at the country club
Pardon me you've done at the country club for the year are you still working?
It is the most devastating news, but it is done and I'm like I'm looking for another job
I do other jobs in between obviously like a farm and stuff, but fuck man
I mean, I have your form you form wait, it's seasonal. That's a seasonal job. Yeah, you're a good time
Yeah, you can't golf in the fucking eight billion feats of snow
That's right. They don't have functions though like like Halloween time or Christmas parties or stuff
Well, okay, so the thing is is the people who
There was a bunch of stuff going on with like management and the people who own it and like family members who have passed away this year
Unfortunately, and like there's just a bunch of stuff that went on and there was a bunch of
Don't know what's going on. I don't know they used to do cross-country skiing and I was like if this was my place
Which honestly I looked into like loans and stuff to see if I could buy it this year because they want under a mill
But I'm like, I'm a fucking Indian. They give me that much money. Anyway
Damn, oh, that's all
You were gonna buy the thing
So I'm gonna put my nor can in the chat so more baby
Make it up
Like I don't see your pillow anymore your big pillow
Mason was his big pillow. I don't know that's why I was asking them
What about like a ski
Um, well, we don't have like ski resort here because like I live in the middle of but fuck nowhere
But we have like if you go to you know, go to the mountains like more so towards like British Columbia
We have like in room and like panorama and then we have Canyon like we do have some ski
Areas around here, but like not like a classy resort. Oh god, but fuck no way. We're in that exactly
It's by uh, it's an Alberta. What's the zip code? None of your fucking zippy business.
Well, one three fuck off. One three fuck off Alexander McQueen. None of you. Oh my god,
I love to because visit that town. But fuck. No way. No, Alex, I think you had a cat. You
Wait, what makes it? I would say I think he had the pillow by
Yeah, that's his piggy pillow man. He loves it. That's piggy pillow. Yeah
I would call it psych. No, that's crazy
No, his name is tuxedo. Oh tuxedo. Yeah
So he's black with some white
He looks like Adolf Hitler
Both you're bugging now. You lost me. He's black. He's white. He's eight. Oh
Yeah, this conversation I'd rather stick with Mason and the piggy pillow
My god
Hey Mason, you know he went
No, I was asking Gotti, I mean I was telling Gotti like he wants to go get a beer, that's why he's not here anymore.
You're asking me to tell him.
I'm telling you, I'm in.
Oh, okay.
That's fair.
He does like that.
I forget that you guys are in Cali man all the time.
Even like I wake up at 6 in the morning sometimes and I see them on I'm like these people are crazy
But then I'm like it's only three in the morning over there Mason. You're in Cali, too
You're in California
No, I haven't been to California before good
He's like in the end. That's why you lived there. Oh, he's in the Midwest. Okay
God I'm in a different area you're in a different area of the country, okay
No, in the United States, but not California
Yeah, the country where the fuck you live, man. It's not a fucking secret
What state do you live in Mason don't worry when I crack down Mason we're not gonna find
No, but God, I don't give
Yeah, how are you?
I want you to make up something
Fucking not Kansas about that. No, God, yeah, I don't live in Kansas. I don't live in California. I live in a different state
There's a place called City Island in New York and it's all lobster lobster lobster
He doesn't even like lab stuff. Hey Mason, could you drum for me Mason the drummer? I
Don't have any drums right now
His name is Mason the drummer, but don't
It's like saying
And then they claim you something you're like, I don't have a guitar that's like asking Alex to show his badge
It's not gonna happen
Or face or like anything
She wants to see you man, I'm a mystery from and my no, no, he goes on camera. He looks like shaggy
I've seen Mason, I know what his shirt, I know what Mason's shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what his shirt looks like, I know what
Yeah, Mason come on
Oh, what the fuck I will have my son every day. I just got a new pair of Hilfiger sneakers
Who wears Hilfiger sneakers? I do because I like coming over and I bought a pair of nautical boots
Prices bro, cuz I'm ordering like all my high school gear, but I'm ordering shit
I will buy you a fucking shirt
I
Don't think show
No, I have a whole figure sneakers with dope jeans and then I have this helping the sweater
It's just the whole thing. Let me ask you a question. So you can't maybe Mason you said you don't you you don't take
Mason
You don't sit in the bathtub and then fill the water like fully make it sit in the bathtub and then put me what?
Alexander I don't take showers man like that much man. What a
Bandsome for women, bro. That's gross, bro
The fuck
Dick you go in you fucking take a shower you scrub your balls you think you're going to work in
It takes those cat baths
The bubble baths you put the bubble baths in the oil
Those are on the edge of the tub
The whorebath. Mason don't tell me you put candles around the toe, baby. Back in the day, when I worked in the bars and stuff, we used to go, you know, someone did the walk of shame. You don't put candles? Alright. Cause they do a wet nap bath, which is a whore's bath. That's the disgusting page. You did that?
Do you fart in the in the top mason?
I'm just trying to get to the one shirt thing so I'm working my way
I just want to know why the same shirt every time Mason. Why is why using web apps page?
One of my favorite shirts, that's why I wear the shirt a different time
One of your favorite can I see another one of your favorites one of your favorites implies that you have other favorites
Let me see another favorite my man
Thank God you don't use them okay good good
Not me. No, but like girls that we used to know when they did the walk of shame or that ain't they fuck somebody and didn't go home that night
Oh, please don't those words don't ever come out of your mouth again. You never did that, right? That's nasty. No, I just did that 17 times
No, I never
She visited me but
If you're wiping your cooch with a wet nap, I don't want to know you
Oh my god, you're mine. If you wipe your cooch with a wet nap, I don't want to know you
No, that sounds like a commercial or something some sort
A new product if you wipe your cooch with a wet nap, I don't know almost a song. I don't want to know you
Lose my fucking number, please
Yeah
Get a little joy soap and put it in the rag and just fucking go to town that's all
No, like those Boston Pete the hand wipes. No here. They call it. You know what they call in your computer
We can pass when the person doesn't think a shower. He just wake up and space cologne on himself
He invented it dick
the
you make fun of what you want, but don't make fun of his shirt
hey psych, I can really like people treat me like this
psych, I can wear the same shirt, right?
yeah, pamo, it's the blue and then it fades into gray
psych, you're muted bro
hit the button
look at his hair, he didn't just go get a beer, he just got fucked or something
look at his hair bro
this happens all the time
he went and listened to disturb for 10 minutes and brought his hair back to earth for volume and came back to us
he was fucking dead from the back
real quick
Hey picture page. You gotta change it. It's too hot
manure
We've got
You
What the fuck is condition are you crazy he's only got one kind of conditioner look he's trying to figure out the wires
the wire is fucking them up right now
can't hear you
you keep on knocking but you can't come in
I still can't hear you it's like you keep on knocking
oh fuck
hey mason
yeah
where do you work
You should have answered Mason you don't work. No
How do you buy clothes? What do you do doesn't dick? He has one shirt. What are you guys trying to join me nuts?
No, we know this. I'm okay the camera, right? I'm okay the camera
Where the fuck are the cameras, bro? Are you kidding? Is that the culture in the closet? We're getting punked
Exactly, exactly. I'm getting punked by both of you or three years actually. I'm about to read my walls apart. Where the fucking cameras
This feels like that this feels like the og like the good old days
Oh, look, I was in the patrol car. Did you see that he was in the patrol car?
Why would you get money out guy, you know, you're not supposed to give money out guys
You know, no if you need money
Don't give money out Mason. We'll hook you up
Got it you need to save your money though, so that's why I can't give it out
I didn't say I was gonna I didn't say I was gonna give you money. I said we'll get you money if you need money
Mason do you spend your money on your one shirt? Yeah, but God he said we though who is we though?
I said we the community
He hates women. Yeah, it's a fact. Hey, guess what Mason? I'm gonna make you love women motherfucker
Just beat the piss out of him
Yeah, oh you're gonna it'll be a love-hate relationship. I promise
Mason talk to Paige
Yeah, no is the answer what you're telling me though
Be nice to page you avoid me like the plague hey Mason say my name a hundred times hey page ask me 65 questions
And the crickets
You get shy
He's doing no Gotti. It's just
I don't care no Gotti. It's not that it's just I don't want to talk to somebody like, you know
What female?
No, I don't want to talk to somebody. It's like different about things
Nobody's different your fucking words carefully Mason somebody's different about things a female
You're very different and you are about everything and so I'm not judging you
Or I do not like you. You know, I think you're cool. So whatever, but I won't know page
I never said no page. I never said I hate you or anything like that page. I don't see anything like that
You know what the word imply means you implied so
No page. I never said anything that's against like, you know, I said just different different means it could be anything different
Maybe that's a bad idea
What's a bad idea God you talking to Paige
It might be I
Mean like the fact that it went so fucking eerily dead quiet like you know what Mason we're cool, okay?
Let's keep it that way
No Mason Mason Mason do you like Paige you think she's pretty
No, I was just here just to chill though, that's all I'm doing.
He said no.
That's double no.
I got double no.
No, but do you think Paige is a pretty girl?
Look, it's like he's loving it.
Look.
He's psyched.
You'd allow someone to treat me like that on your panel?
I don't give a fuck.
I'm sorry, Paige.
I'm sorry.
Mason, behave yourself.
Are you hitting on Paige, Mason?
No, I didn't say anything hateful psyche. She said that I didn't want to talk to her
I just didn't feel like talking to her psyche. Isn't she a pretty girl though? She's pretty huh?
No, she's okay. Like I don't have like I'm not saying thing. Oh my god. She's okay
She's okay
No, she's okay. Yeah
I have like I have like six five shirts
Damn
Send them five send them at least five is about your build
Mason have you ever felt the breast have you ever touched the boom? That's mason's type. No, you know
No, I'm Sandra. I've never done that. No
Wait
No moves at all. No, don't you know squeeze the book now sucked on a nipple. Nothing. That's a nip. I mean, you know
Fuck are you cooking up on your head?
That's Pam. That's Pamela. His name is Pamela when he had the wig on.
It looks like Cogwebala. Oh, he's Pamela?
Yeah, it's Pam. Yeah, it's Pamela.
Thank you. Why would you wear a wig though? I don't understand.
Pamela, wake and stare at me.
Pamela, wake and there you go.
You catch on quick, my man.
This is exactly what it is.
Amazing thought. Maybe this is the figure that I'm wearing.
Yeah
So now he's in Cognito. You put on a wig, psyche makes you feel better. That's why you wear a wig
Is it because you're do you find me attractive yet?
Yeah, but you want to wear it psyche wouldn't want to wear you hold on
We're just gonna we're just gonna completely pass that he's never touched a boob thing
Hey Mason, why haven't you done something?
What the fuck?
Hey, Paige, what's this going to look like down the slide?
30 years, man.
One move has been squeezed.
I mean, whatever.
We can go with Saki's wig, whatever.
Let's go with Saki's wig.
Just fucking hanging.
Mason, have you ever touched a boo?
Yeah.
No, it's new.
It's new to me.
It's new?
OK.
Yeah.
It's new to you.
It's something I haven't done yet. It's like you haven't got that fart yet. You never drank breast milk. What's wrong with you? No
Where have you been
Do you know what you take it for a little sweet, yeah, I know what it's for
It's not what is it for and don't say just don't say peeing
We won't say it's for being my man. I'm in it was all right. Well, I came the cameras
Where's it can the key? Oh, I stink culture get out of the closet motherfucker. I know you're in here you piece of shit
God, let's be honest
God, let's be honest. You're supposed to go to the restroom when you go to the restroom. So like that's what you use it for
Yes, there is one of its purposes. What's the other purpose Mason? Why are you signaling me out of the penis?
There's three people up here. Why are you all right? All right, Mason. Does your dick ever get hard for no reason?
And then it feels a weird and like fun like take a lean fuzzy and like you're like what the hell is this?
No, it does know certain things happen like that. You can't control. Yeah, Alexander
Yeah, like it just all of a sudden. It's just like go hard and you know, it's just stick in
What do you think that is?
Yeah, something like that, but I mean I don't really have no control over that kind of stuff
Hey Mason always smile says you should go visit psych
in person
Do when you look at a girl's ass Mason a woman's ass you like it
When you look at a woman's ass does your dick get hard
Mason and psyche when you look at a woman's lips or face or tits or body does your dick get hard
It's supposed to be something like that, but now I don't really go through that. I mean, you know, okay
Jason, but he said he's not homosexual though
Mason anything sexual. He's he's just
Just you and your delightful shirt you like men and an end or you like you like the ladies. Yeah
So you narrate
You know, you narrate a vagina, you know, put a vagina in your mouth and stuck your tongue inside the her pussy hole and
Credit for that
Fuckin' facts, okay.
No Paige, I like women, but I don't really do anything with the women, I just, you know,
hang out.
I mean, I'm talking to women sometimes in here.
Well, that's good as long as you're nice about it, which sometimes I notice maybe there's a little bit of a misconception
I feel like you have respect so that for women to the point where you might you know
Like it could just keep doing what you're doing, but maybe do it a little different
All right, hold on though Mason Mason women though. He's stuck the few
All right, no, so his dick gets hard when he sees women. He doesn't know why would you suck psyches peepee?
No, would that interest you
No, but I don't go that far with guys though. Oh, okay. You don't like stuff like that. You think that's gross
Yeah
What if he does it to you though, I
Mean would you guys
We're just talking here, okay brothers brothers amongst brothers
Psycho's not against it
No, no, he's not against it Mason actually you would love it
I'm just here just to hang out. I'm not trying to be think sexual in here. I'm just trying to come here
Just well
Expand the horizons, but you know, you know used to say that
I used to say that same shit and I look you're not just a spirit
You're also flesh my friend. You're not just a voice on the internet
You also have a body that needs you know, so ficing and you know it needs stuff
Yeah
No, we need to suffice our sexual pledges
You want to suffice me page
What would you just say no, I don't
If she wants to suffice to me advise or survive
So flies, I don't know
No, she doesn't know surprising for fucking spend the Rella
Spend the rest of us each other
Yeah, only in your fucking little demented mind
Page page, I know we have a body we're supposed to do stuff for their body, but it matters what we do
Exactly what you supposed to do with it is take that thing that gets hard and put it between pages legs and ram it in that hole
She has
Okay, so now well you pick Mason. That's up to you. No
We got you brother
Yeah
That's up to you brother
They don't go
Page doesn't do that Alex. Come on. What are you crazy? You saw the feet I'm a nice fucking lady
But I know white girls with dirty feet take it harder than any girl on the planet white. I'm white ish, okay
Canadian dirty feet
Yeah, because I'm a ninja my man. I got picture everybody's feet up here. Show it show it then show it
I guess you're out of the
Because I'm a T right like I'm mixed blood for sure your black foot
I am the black one, I'm looking for it, hold on.
Let's prove it, Alex.
I got you, hold on, I'm looking for it, hold on.
He's going through his feed files.
Hold on baby. I got my pictures in there. I got you little black foot. I
Got like 30 of them though, which one do you want? I got you running from the fucking golf club. I got you picking it
Oh, here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. You want hold on. You want the close-up? I'm gonna give you this one first
Hold on first, I'm gonna give you this one. Okay
Yeah, nobody no page. You're right. No page. You're right earlier. You have to share the panel with other people
We can't just be here for yourself. Yeah, I can understand that's right darlin. That's right. That's right. It's fair game
We're all up here all doing the same thing, you know
but different oh
My god, you're so fucking slow Alex who we all start roasting him now Mason
Why he's taken so long
Posting image. Oh
I can't wait. Let's see. What's up?
Hey, I was just waiting for psyche to come back. It's like it's gone and he hasn't came back
Yeah, he had to witching to do he'll be back
I don't know how I feel about that. Are you talking to yourself or about my feet?
Page is feet. There you go. You don't need a job. You can just do the feet stuff
Well, no
Pardon me Mason
Alexander was talking about getting with the page like you want to do stuff
Alex got a side hustle. I
Forgot Mason's very literal. He's very loud. Um, so
That's just not gonna happen Mason. It's just jokes
I thought he was being serious though with the page. I don't know who's serious on here. Nobody's serious on here, dude
No, pay the study is being serious
Get it with you and stuff. No, I got I got I got the whole collection
But when I go to edit avatar
No, no, no, I go to edit avatar and then I go to add picture and then I go to the picture
And then it tells me to like like a box it in and then the only option is x I'll go back
So it doesn't let me save it. What are you on my upload of pictures? So
Hey Alex, remember when you told us how easy it would be to run a panel and how all you could just go click, click, click, click, because we're all
Yeah, you can, you can do click, click, click
Let me see if I have it
You should just say sorry, because it was rude
First of all
Hey, what did he do that was weird or what did he do that was rude?
Alexander likes to talk a lot with his mouth and his mouth is faster than his than his actions sometimes or in mind
Experience is all I meant by that but he's he's page. Hey, did you like the way he was talking to you or what happened?
No, he's fine. I've since day one him and I whatever he is Alexander
But no, he didn't mean it in a in an actual logical sense
Like he's just we're all just like it's jokes and stuff, right? Like we're all just friends
So he wasn't so page he wasn't serious about like trying to be with you and trying to date you and see you and stuff
God, no, no, no Mason. He was not
God, hey, that was a picture.
Huh. No, it wasn't.
No, that was a picture of you, Mason.
No, it wasn't. Come on.
Hey, do you saw a picture like, didn't you?
I did see a picture.
Didn't you see the same picture, Mason?
Because we both have we have both of this.
We have eyes that are looking at the same thing, right?
Yeah. That's what I'm saying, Paige.
It was a picture that Goddy was trying to show you, I think, or something.
I bet. Yeah.
Yeah, it was. And who was it of Mason?
Was it of you?
I would think so she loved it. I would think so she loved it
Mason I've seen your little face a million times before on this shirt and all the whole all the you up here
I have just cuz
When I was on here
That's correct mason. You're right. I mean I have in the chat, but I haven't been up here
I have I took a little break from YouTube for a bit there
What did you ever say page? What'd you ever say to me that I would only remember though?
So I don't remember talking to you or anything before. Oh, well, no just in the chat and I actually just
address
How nice your shirt was and you didn't you know
Hey, that's one thing we ever said to each other before
Yeah, it was just hi nice shirt Mason. That was it
That was it Mason. She likes the shirt, bro
Hey, I don't remember
Pays I don't remember just having that conversation because we didn't really say much before you've got it in well
That's because Mason. I think that sometimes you don't either pay too much attention to the chat or not enough
No, I do pitch it to the chat, but I talk on to psyche when I'm on here pretty much
Yeah, we know. Yeah, we know I
Mean also the Goddy when he's here, but mostly when it's just psych and I him and I just pretty much talk like on here
Yeah, on the panel people people that you respect and people that you feel comfortable with right?
Yes, what I'm saying. That's what I was explained to psyche early. I only talk to people. I feel comfortable with talking to
Yep
Well, that's fair because earlier didn't you didn't really know me and now that we're having a conversation and hopefully you feel comfortable enough
but don't ask me 85 million questions because
I'll answer the same at use time
Wait, what do you mean you'll answer on this page? What do you mean you'll answer in the same?
I mean the same way or the same kind of way
Well, I will answer it accordingly and directly and if necessary of change in the
direction tone or any other
I guess way of projecting an answer to you then I will adjust it
But otherwise if you ask the same question, I'll probably give it the same answer if it's the same thing
Yeah, but I don't I try not to do that. No page. I try not to do that as much like that's the same question
I know you don't try to it's your favorite thing though in the world and it's okay because we love you for it
Honestly every time I like that. I have a good page. I like to ask different things
No page. I like to ask different things too. Not just the same things all the time
Okay, so let me do this. Let's let's try an exercise
So I'm gonna bring up the color blue and then you're gonna ask me three different questions about that
Like, you know, you could go. Yeah, so I'm gonna say blue and you're gonna ask me three different questions about the color blue
That's it right there
That's your foot page
I'm not my fucking foot.
It is.
That's the norm there looks like Cinderella's sister's feet.
That's not right.
No, no, bro.
I have 34 pics of her, all 30 feet down.
I just can't put her up.
But I can put up all the pigs which is weird. I could put up psych. It's a supply
I'm protected violently protected
And I want to drop to do it, but then I won't be able to come up because so psych is not here
That's okay. What's he taking a shit?
He doesn't take this long to take a shit. He takes anybody except for like dads who are trying to avoid their entire household
Don't take 45 to an hour minute shit
Just gonna relax you just sit there and relax you do your work in the
Earrling monkey feet because I'm just little online shopping
Gabbling like what does he put in a fucking everything he's just doing everything other than this
Literally everything else he needs to get away sometimes
Neil Patrick Harris will return for the new Harold and tumor but sources say he could make a cameo in the movie
Nope
Isn't that doogie how's it new Patrick?
Doogie fucking doogie
That's Tugi Hauser, MD.
He did that show.
Well, that's actually super tiny. He's someone's is a size 12. Yeah
He's saying you were running in dirt you were running in dirt and they were little yeah
I go do you know why a golf without like I have golf shoes. They're really expensive. They're really nice
I love them. I see for two years for them now listen
I golf without shoes because I am grounding and
Golfing the double G
Trinity it's not Trinity like joy golfing and grounding. That's that's the Holy Trilogy
You ever think of birdie?
I actually you guys I'm so stoked this year I
Got a par on every single not a birdie
But I got a par on all of like my biggest challenges that I set out like I couldn't even oh I can fuck golf course up
That's awesome, man. Oh, I'm so happy and I did it like I had to learn how to golf all over again after my injury
Because I didn't stop golfing with my injuries and my crutches
And so I kind of had to like learn it taught me a lot actually having that kind of I don't want to say the word
Hany cat but like just like on my actual golf game in a sense that like
I had to work around it and teach myself new things and actually now I'm an even better golfer
Yeah, I did I had I had a bunch of shit going on like I have to slip disk in my lower back
That's still a thing. Oh Alexander McQueen. That is not nice. Oh shit
That's not the picture dude. That's that's the wrong one damn page. I didn't know that
That's not my dirty black feet. That's horrible, man. I hope you're feeling better
Yeah, no, it's okay. I had like sprained ribs and a torn muscle under my shoulder blade
I had and my hip and my femur. I still actually have to go get x-rays again. I'm still on crutches
Jesus
Yeah, fuck. I know
It's hard core. It's a hard core. Hey, I'm still trying to put pages feet up and I put up a cock
No, it's coming baby 30 feet are coming. He's the last thing I do
No, no, that was well, I pressed the wrong button, bro. Don't tell us like he's sleeping. He doesn't even know
don't spill the beans. Alexander beans. Nothing's gonna happen. Don't snitch. Don't be a snitch.
All right. Heavy, heavy Friday night fucking. Nobody, nobody's for nothing.
No, I didn't see anything. Did you cut? Did you pay six?
Damn, it's your fault. I'm trying to get 30 feet up there, man. I hit the wrong button
I knew what I was like wait a minute why is that up there what the fuck I didn't press
I didn't press done, I didn't press done, I didn't press done for it to go up, it just like completely, it automatically switches
You know?
Ah, fuck
Alex, I'm gonna say fuck like you say it, fuck, you say fuck like me, like a comedian
Jesus, if he wakes up, don't let him, let him sleep, let him get a good night's sleep before that
He's happy right now
You don't have to have surgery on your disk do you no I don't it's not like it's okay good
Yeah, no, it's not that severe. Thank goodness. Yeah, that's that would suck
Yeah, I feel like the bionic woman though. It's the fucking bitch. I got extendos my like long fucking metal arms
I just feel like I'm I don't know. I'm fast though. You need a lot of heat therapy. I
Need like oh my my chiropractor. I got a new one and guess what?
He's fucking hot it's so weird
Right you can't like get your little back all crunched and then let a little to rip or something because then you're like damn
Blade Hamilton won't like me anymore
Is he doing all the moves he's he's telling you turn on your side and he put your leg up and all that stuff and pushes on it
He yeah, he did like all of the medical slash. Yeah medical
He did the things that he's like like got a fucking doctorate for which was really really nice
And then he also has really great eyes, but his hair stupid
He's got it like if you remember in grade six and everybody had that fucking like little like gelled up front part
everything else is like
Super slicked up anyways, it looks like a fucking BMX jump his hair looks like a BMX jump like you're asking for his number
You can hook him up with new hair his name is blade and his hair looks like a BMX jump
But he doesn't have his own he just has no chiropractic or whatever. You're gonna make me bomb you again
the
Yeah, that's crazy
He goes no, he's fucking super white dude
I practice oh my gosh, he's like white is like actually if he lifted his shirt up
It probably looks like psychs fucking little are you gonna fuck him in the time of factor always like an important
Are you gonna fuck this brain son in the office one day?
Like, just oops.
No, I didn't one fucking time because I was in pain.
And like, I never went back yet, because I'm just-
Oh, you've been jerking off to America since?
Yeah, I flicked my bean vigorously blade.
He might be the one.
Come on.
Well, which other way is there to flick it, baby?
You never know.
Like, so many ways.
There's so many ways.
Vigorously.
Oh, blade, blade, blade.
Oh, blade.
the
I also said that I didn't really know all sounds like he's a fucking sex
He's got six year old's hair, but he has his own like practice and he is a doctor in a sense
And he is cute and that was it but those three things are definitely not enough for me to be like oh blade
I'm swoon over you. Oh my god. Does he have a ring? Is he married for the perfect man?
He's never gonna come you know that is he married
His name is blade. He's never gonna come. Obviously. It's so picky. It's so picky. Come on. I'm really not picky
Loving and I just don't want to be taken advantage of again ever you want to meet a guy named Dean
You blame a guy named no name and no guy. I just don't want to meet anybody
I don't give a fuck anymore. Like I'm just well played is just for fucking all right play
It's not someone you're gonna marry the universe
Just fucking brains out in the office and get it over with we're gonna find you a rich man
Someone who's a fuck Alex apparently because he's always
Yeah, well introduce me to play
Introduce me to play since he's a hot dude leave my chiropractor alone
Like stop trying to fuck a chiropractor man come on like that's an expensive fuck
You'd have to fly all the way over here
And then you'd have to like book a chiropractor appointment to be like 120 bucks for that plus like it's fucking like I don't know
maybe $800 ticket and place to stay because you ain't staying at my fucking house and
You would like probably
You'd probably get beat up and then you'd have to go to the hospital because you say fuck wrong
And your intentions aren't good so you tell me I would have to spend $1,500 to go there to get beat up and
For the universe to be like, you know what Alexander and you belong in America
And you're just gonna slap me in the face with lobster and send me on my way
No, not unless you bring a lobster and a styrofoam cooler of ice on the plane
Because we don't have that shit over here unless you go like to be seen
You don't have a lobster in fucking Canada. What kind of freak place is it?
Yeah, we do, but it's different. It's a rock lobster. You know what I mean?
Like Atlantic and Pacific is completely different. You don't have the hairy lobster. There's a hairy one.
Paige, why don't you monetize your channel? Why don't you do it? Why don't you do your monetize?
You have a hairy lobster. I know you do.
What I want to know God was speaking pardon me. I was saying why don't you monetize your channel so you can get some cash
Okay, well, I'll just call you to be like hey am I cool enough? She's not a hooker bro. She's not gonna
Celeres well if I quit slacken and I actually
Hey, I've been doing a lot of artwork. I'm actually working on a tarot deck right now. You can do fucking pay by nobody doesn't count page
You can sell that stuff on Etsy. Paint by fucking thought doesn't count, Alex.
Pay by nobody, I've been doing a lot of art.
Man, it's just Canadian history.
Oh, you're a little familiar with your brain or fucking everything.
You had mad people in your room. I remember you used to have like a thousand people when you did your readings and stuff.
That was like twice.
You shut the fuck up
Panicked and fled your own path. That's twice. I got a big mouth and I don't like lobster
How is the little kitty cat with me for beans for being
Raven Raven and tuxedo
Let's be tuxedo is tuxedo there
the
Remember you put those up. They were kind of dirty, but if she was outside, so it's cool
Look at his little face
Put his paw. That's a new cat. Yes, his name is flex. What the fuck? What's his name flex?
Look at I did some artwork. Oh nice
Yeah, what artwork? Where's the artwork?
Right there. Oh, okay. Oh, okay. That looks like art actually. That's abstract. That is good. How do you do that?
It's fluid art
the
Oh, here's Raven
Do you sell them? Can I buy that one of those off you? Can you put in a frame?
So I'll give you a deal
Right, so either I start off someone starts auctioning them off. No, I'm just kidding
Um, how about I would do because they're kind of a set I would do
All three for 30 bucks? Maybe 40?
30 bucks? Yeah, 100 bucks, at least.
Shut up.
You know, this is the problem. I've never actually sold a piece of my artwork. I've always just
given it away or made it with the inspiration.
No, but all three were for 30 bucks, 100%.
Alex, you're worth more than 30 bucks. So maybe my artwork might be too.
How about, how about this? How about, how about, how about 55?
55. You got it.
Dollars or doll hairs, because this is, I'm just kidding.
American money too, not Canadian.
Yeah. Paisos, no, not pesos. I mean, Colombian.
Why the fuck would it be pesos?
None of us are there.
Why are you
Can you show the art again
Why did you ask that with like fear and
And then then when I look close, it's like it looks it's like SpongeBob or some shit
They sell those that sell those at $90 a piece. You're gonna make money trust me
I have I have a ton of stuff that I have made posted on my YouTube
I'd like in the very beginning days. There's like a hundred years. I'm a fucking dinosaur. Why don't you just put up an Etsy store? I
Think it's all right. Why are you biting my Achilles then in you? There we go. Look at this
You know where you put that in the bathroom every time you go stream look at that
Those are nice. I like that look at that
Right in a nice frame
This is a page original artwork exactly. Yeah, I'll pay 30 dots for that. I'll give you 50 for that
100% I would love that
Fabulous sold
No, God hush
You're gonna say it sir. You're like sold
Go boys going twice
So Alexander McQueen in the back. I like something a little more
Something that I can identify
Black with lots of gold do you have
Something like a kitty or like a like a house so go like a cat smoking a cigar farm or draw that cat
Like you have there that little Nazi cat
but can you draw things to like a cat like things like that or it's just like that abstract art like the
Can you do clouds and a sunset
Had to pee said just you're muted for a moment. Hmm
Can you draw yourself peeing
Can you draw yourself fucking off?
With the little panties around the raincoats, you know, like go to the toilet, imagine that, bro.
24 by 15 inch on the wall
Baby
She doesn't need to draw it. Oh my god. Yes, I can draw. Yes. I work with alcohol and I make pottery
I have
Pottery
I do all kinds of stuff like yarn work. I can my for me. I have
Work, what the hell you doing here? You could be making mad money. Exactly. What are you doing on the golf course?
Maybe you should be put no no the golf course was good. That was fun
Golf for me is like that's a passion. Golf is a lifestyle. All right. Well, you got a yarn yourself something sucks
So the feet don't get dirty
I don't wear socks to sell
No, I got pictures of dirty feet on the golf course
The only actually needs to see one little shot and that's it. You're finished
85 fucking million shots. I do and I'm so fucking upset I can't put them up right now and
Anything a cock pops up. So exactly. Exactly. What the fuck just gonna relax till I'm sober tomorrow
I'll figure that tomorrow. I'll show it tomorrow. Trust me. If I gotta make a new account or whatever
With your feet at the moment. No, it's you
It was you goffing away, you know going live and then you had the sandals on and you took them off
And then you were running and then the bottom of your feet were mad dirty
And I was like look at this screenshot screenshot screenshot screenshot screenshot. It was the best
And I was like, I'm gonna fuck with her.
I'm gonna fuck with her.
If she ever says help to me again,
I'm gonna just throw up 30 feet.
So instead of me shooting shitties against you,
I'll just like beat you in the pocket.
Of course, what do you think I do?
Fucking mouse aggressive.
That's what I do, baby.
That's why I don't come up ever.
So you can't screenshot shit.
I guess what you got a dirty mouth. I know I do baby. Fuck you're weird
I'm so weird. It's scary
But I'm not lucky with the dirty pee thing and it's it's clear as day
Do you want to go of course? It's a sunny day and it's a big Irish feed and it's you and oh
I know the position and but the feet and it's as close in ever like zoom in shots and outshots both feet one foot
Are you good at golf and then I'm like my god in the grass be that dirty or
It's just you know, she just dirty feet from home
Dirty obviously the grass. I don't know. It's a little too dirty
And yeah, I think that may be home feet that might be home dirty feet
Listen up. I'm a country girl. I'm also an Indian and I just like to do what I do and you do what you do and
That's that
Fuck you walk around with your bare feet in the city streets. I don't know you went and you're in line
I mean here in New York, you know, you take your shoes off a little bit and you walk feet are dirty
It turns me on to be honest because wipe it dirty feet are like good in bed for some reason
I used to think that was a nasty shit seeing girls walk in the streets of the city barefoot
But when they're hot white girls
It puts it a little like
It's like walking around it like fuck it was a boondestock 90 fuck in the 90s one
That's gross. Yeah, I'm not putting that in my mouth fuck that you're just getting what is the hell no
but you put them in the air you'll you'll you'll see the dirty feet going up into the air like wow this bitch wants cock
You know what I'm saying as the feet are going up like that's one dirty foot this bitch wants
It's just like an indicator of how bad she wants to go
for a minute because they matter
There's a chat
Look it's a Halloween time God look at that
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo
That's
Shit that picture
You look so hot in that picture
Hang it from her nose, huh? Oh, yeah, I had to change my picture
That's great
Because I had a really had a big old fucking bat in the cave
The last time that like my last one and it was funny kid was there
Yeah, cuz you're a fucking true friend. Yeah, exactly
If I had anything wrong with anything and none of you told me whole motherfuckers. I won't be telling you none
I'm just kidding. Okay, so
Yeah, okay, well the fact that you guys both zoomed in one on my feet and one on my fucking nose
You guys need hobby is yeah, that's our hobby
That's not a good one
Are there anybody left in here? There's nobody
Oh, it's 32 people here. There is people here. Oh shit
Don't know why the thumbnails my foot pick. Oh, that's great. You're you're Cinderella sister
Holy shit, oh
Ravey, yeah, she was I'll go back out. She's
Is Wanda drinking? Oh, wow
I am a little bit Wanda's drinking too cheers Wanda suck girl
Okay, I'll never do that again. I promise
What am I gonna go live again Jamie um
Probably okay. I want to do an art tutorial. Just watch me make a fucking sandwich. I'm sure that you
stone i might add out of my fucking tree um i'm sure that you'll watch me uh paint
all your videos are fun the cooking videos the tarot shit that's all good stuff and golf you
know you just gotta mix it up a bit oh the golf i saw a few golf ones yeah they're pretty good
okay so now there's gonna be a lot more other things that i do that i like because that's
And I know I sound like a four, but you never did so I didn't really watch those. Okay, you know what?
What you're gonna go for like I've been in charging professional competitions
And so I'm gonna have to start yelling for so you can be my four coach
If you don't do it, you're not gonna win
It's that simple
Well, I live in the fucking boonies in the mountains and like
If I do you want to win or do you want to lose?
Honestly, I golf with no shoes on rain or shine. I golf with grizzly bears. I
Fucking don't know if I should yell for like
Sometimes it's not necessary, right?
Like with a bear coming at you
I don't have time to yell for I'm watching my back. I'm fucking finding my shoes
I got shit to do. Okay, you got to carry a gun on the course
uh actually for a bit I did yeah you might need it well what the fuck's
bear amaze gonna do first of all that's way too close for it to be effective if
a bear is that close for you to have for the bear amaze to be effective you're
fucked honestly a gun's not gonna work on a grizzly either though look at Alex
left to go fucking figure out why you can't post my feet
I've never heard him. No, I've never heard him so quiet. I've never heard such an eerie style
It's probably got a thousand pictures. I
Know I bet he does though. That's got everything Alex got pictures of dudes. He's got fucking everything
He's hiding everything except for himself. There's something he's got on everybody
Well, fuck man. He needs hobbies too other than being a
being a YouTube
Yeah, YouTube streets fucking whistleblower
Detective Alex. Yeah, what would we do without him?
Probably be fine
Like in the sense of like not getting fucking yelled at and and fucking New York
You still doing the readings
Yeah, I always I'm always like I'm not just a terror reader. I'm a medium, right?
So I'm always channeling and so he's a lot going on for me
Quick one if you don't mind or you're gonna say honestly if you want me to do one for you
I don't mind. Yeah, you know, I hate to ask but if you don't mind
You hate to ask God does not hate
Remember, don't worry about the real God hates. Okay. You're like, you're like, don't worry about what I do. Okay. The real God hates
Oh fucking right, you know what all of us people who said fuck a little bit too much on the internet
We're gonna be behind a big long line of others and when I mean quotations others, you know who I mean
We got a special plan for you people
Yeah, it's not a good one. There's no light. There's no light, but you're used to it. So you can live in the dock
Okay, that was fucking weird. Don't let me do that again
And I know that you like your original and you like the rider weight. Yes, that's my favorite
I know I know just cuz I've been gone for a bit doesn't mean I don't know. Yeah, the car bear card deck
It's just a little too cutesy for me all that other stuff
Yeah, no, that's not your thing. Let me go get my OG writer wait
It is the one my mom actually gave me before she passed away. So let's go get that quick. Thank you
Yeah, you're most welcome just a moment
Okay, I found it. Also, Jamie here. Here's Rick. You say hi to Jamie. Oh, that's a good girl. There you go
You know what every time I use this deck it's for you and it's just kind of like a
It's um, it's very special because like I said my mom gave it to me
It's awesome. I thank you again. Yeah, and it's like oh gee like it's old as fuck like she was old old thing
I was kidding
My mom was only like
My mom wasn't even 60. Oh 61. I'm almost like 61. All right
Okay, here we go
Let me clear the energy of the deck and myself
I'm not gonna go
On video right now because I don't fucking feel like it. No, that's fine
But I know that you trust me
Gonna do a shuffle and a knock
Get out of here spirit all the bad ones just kidding. I don't know my problem is I just feel like Jim Carrey tonight
I got him talking accent
I think I just missed everybody and I'm super stoked right now.
Yeah, it's good to have you back.
Thanks.
It's always nice to have a warm welcome and instead of a go fuck yourself.
I mean, I did scare away like everyone else on the panel, so I'm not,
I'm not feeling great about that, but that's okay because it's...
No, I think they just fell off.
It's like you're sleeping, you can't let anybody back.
Hit and then sleep live say slash like some side tarot slash slender
Okay, you ready
Okay, here we go here do we go
Um, so before the cards even flip, I do feel like crossroads right now.
I don't know if you're trying to make a decision between two things.
I feel like maybe actually more than two things.
There's some like shift going on within your, in like, in your deepest self.
So, you know, like, let's say...
Not the first house not the second house, but you know like you can keep on knocking, but you can't come in
Whatever it is that you're trying to decide you're still very guarded on like the decision itself
It's like almost like you're protecting it and you're not super open to voicing it
Which is unusual for you because you are not
you are not scared to speak up or voice anything
that you're thinking, feeling, or seeing.
So this must be very personal for you.
And I feel like it's something that's gonna change
the trajectory of your life in the sense of like,
that's why you're keeping it so kind of like down low,
even though I just voiced it,
but you only, you know what it means anyways.
Like-
No, no, I know exactly what you're talking about.
Yeah.
Okay, um, I don't know why you're so worried about what your family is going to think because again
I mean me to know you on you know, I mean even just picking up your I know your energy
It's not like I know I don't know you like personally personally. I've never hung out with you in person, but
Um, I do know all of you because I can
Invasively tap into your body into your soul into your feelings all of it right wired right in and I do know that that's also
Unlike you so I feel like you're also questioning why the fuck am I being so unlike myself
But also feeling like a very strong version of a different version. Does that make any fucking sense?
Okay, okay, so let's start with the cards now that I've said what I've had to say
Also, are you having abdominal issues, whatever, like an uneasiness in your stomach?
Not lately, but I did a few months ago, I did.
Okay, and did you get that taking care of or looked at into any kind of depth?
It had, yeah, I had it looked at and I'm working my way through it. It's better than it was.
Okay, so it's been a process and it's going to be one, but like if I was you any little
Tiny like inclination that there might be something that feels off
I do want you to go to the hospital immediately just because I feel like this is also a very tender health
Issue I'll call it an issue because it's not a condition yet, but like it can become a condition if
You don't I also are you eating the right things? Like are you trying to stay true to some sort of kind of consistency?
You need to make sure that you stick to that. Okay
No, I don't need the right things, but no I I have a physical I have a one coming up. So
I'm gonna see what they say
Yeah, sounds good. Okay. Yeah, because I like I'm not a medical. Well, I mean I did go to med school
I'm not a medical professional with a degree, but I can advise you that
just be just be um
We don't like to admit this and this is you know, but you know how my readings are I mean
Just be just be easy on your yourself in the sense of like don't
Don't cause yourself that angst like if if humanly possible
Like little stress and anxiety because it's just like those are the two things that I feel like trigger. I don't know if it's like a
Would you call that an ulcer? I try not to yeah, I try not to let those things get to me
Okay, so that being said we're gonna set it aside and I would like to know some
Things from the how many cards do I actually fuck it? We're not gonna ask you that question
You're gonna get as many as you get
Okay. Okay, here we go.
All right. So right off the get go, we do have the page of ones in the reverse. Okay.
So
Something has been affecting your drive but your passion your creativity and your ability to like kick it into high gear
So you're kind of like but you're also like this in the reverse is like I'm not a fuck boy
I'm I'm a nice man. You know what I mean? Like this is this is a gentleman rather than like us like a
What do you call it like a rico suave? I don't know what you call it, you know
So that's good. I feel like you're just changing some
I do see you like I said at this crossroads and even looking at this card like I will show you
them laid out in a minute. I do feel like
with with the anxiety with the stomach issues and and like the you're not feeling quite yourself like this card in the reverse is like
Gaudi in the reverse a little bit
But I feel like it's because of this shift that you're going through to make it which in
long term is going to help you make this decision of
What we discussed at the beginning of the reading so that makes a lot of sense actually
Yeah, it does
Okay, so
What else do we have?
All right, okay, and I feel like you're coming to like kind of like a
Consensus so because the seven of cups in the reverse is like, okay, I'm not looking at all of these options anymore
I am now
Okay, so in the shuffle I did have the devil come out in the upright so the double what I have the devil in the upright
Oh the devil
Yeah, let me flip it over.
Oh, shit.
The point's coming out in the reverse, which is fine.
I'm not making decisions anymore, but I'm also done being this person.
This version of myself is now no longer.
And I'm also...
Coming down to a decision because now there's like you know what I mean like if this isn't the upright
This would be like oh, I'm trying to make all these decisions, and I don't know what to choose TV TV
You know what I mean, but we have it in the river
So I'm done being this person
I'm still a part of that person, but I'm done making this this decision isn't going to hold me back anymore
I have now come to a consensus
But what does hold you back is something to do with this decision or has it's it's linked to something that might be toxic and or that
the
Bad might outweigh the good, but there is a great outcome. It's just maybe not about like the oh
With a decision that comes of like gain or bounty. Does that make sense?
So it might be something bad, but something good will eventually come out of it. Yes, you're like, okay
So at this crossroads, I do see that this it's like, okay
So this path has a bunch of light and has no obstructions
But this path does have darkness and obstructions. I do know that the there's greater gain
Not only with just like probably material things or with monetary things, but with lessons and and things for your soul
So it could be a bit of a dark night of the soul
I'm choosing to go on this darker path to
Embrace a brighter light when I come out of it to change myself in a sense and it's almost like you're not
It's not like it's it's not only that you're you're aware, but divine is
Deciding for you or with you. Does that make sense? I totally because I'm always walking
I'm always walking the edge of a light dark my life. Oh me too me too. Absolutely. I love living in both
And I mean, I'm sorry if you don't like me anymore after that, but like I'm true to it
You know, that's that's a yin and the yang
That's where I'm confident in myself knowing that I accept that I am dark
I accept that I am light and I have been in both at their fullest and I love them combined exactly
Balance is everything. I live my life like that always always live like that. It's great. Oh
Okay
I'm going to have an out card or an out card an outcome card. I
Don't know why I just wanted to talk like a hobbit like ah, let's have an outcome
But you know what I mean like what the fuck was that?
Leave it's the weird canadian to be weird and canadian. Yes, you live in the woods man. It's all that hobbit stuff
Too much fresh air and not enough socialization.
Yeah, see like you're moving away from something that was toxic or the thought of it like you've
accepted it. It's like I've just accepted that this is my decision and everyone else is going to
accept it too and I'm going to move forward and I'm not going to look back. I'm going to put my
Okay, well, let's have one more and then we'll kill beautiful. Yeah, you're coming out of like conflict
You're coming out of inner conflict. You're coming out of outer conflict and you're like, hey
You know what? I know how to fucking handle this and it's not like you're running from it
But I know that I I know that I'm the Empress. I know that I and that's your final card is the Empress and so
Empress, but okay, listen, we're all divine feminine and masculine in Cairo. There is no you know this don't even mess
okay, so
This is beautiful. You've come to a decision that is the best for you and your highest good even though
There is some give-and-take but everything else is like you see that everything else no matter what has that light in that dark
So like fuck it whatever decision you make is going to be for your highest
That's it you just you just summed it up right there when you said fuck it whatever decision I make that's it. Yeah
Because you know your worth, you know your value, and you know what your expectations are and you're not willing to budge on them any longer.
And there won't be any conflict about it because this is your decision and you're moving forward.
Yeah, I never looked at it.
That's it, that's beautiful.
This is just for you. All of it is just you know even karmatic like divine justice from whatever from wherever
Everything's just kind of all evened out. You're squared
Awesome, man. This is perfect. Thank you. You're very welcome. It was wonderful
You summed me up perfectly
Well, you know, I guess I'd have to find something else to do if I didn't pay
Anyways, that was what thank you for letting me do that any time man. Thank you
All right now we can't ignore all to my shammy. What's up?
I'm seeing it post pictures of him holding up the number four hinting him. Oh
God, oh hi chat. I'm gonna read you now. What's up, y'all?
No, the number four is like considered a death symbol
an Asian culture
Think of it as like a death and rebirth, right?
Why were you thinking that were you reading the chat, too did I fucking miss something he just wrote the four number four about four times
Oh, well, I did not do that. I
Live in the middle of nowhere. Okay, just give my leggy fucking
Death is coming for us all
Bakelips, I don't know, that's pretty specific. Um, I don't need the cards for that.
Aw, you need a reading too. Okay, just let me go find my phone charger.
I love symbolism.
I do. Well, there's that's the thing science and synchronicities and symbolism like it's everywhere
And if you haven't you acknowledge recognize and connect it and resonate with it somehow and apply it
Then you're fucking golden that you do that great
You see all the science man. You can see them wherever
It's kind of annoying sometimes
No, it's good though that you can decipher things
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do
Uh
Really that's nothing you're gonna have five more to be I was trying to be coy oh you have five
Oh, you are crazy cat lady. Oh shit. Well, okay. I'm a witch
I'm a page. I'm a like and I honestly I
Don't go I didn't go to the pet store and I was like I need five cats more. Ha ha ha ha. You know what I mean like
Yeah, they just came to you
Yeah, I didn't like this littlest one. What do they call it? It's a familiar
They are my owls and cats are my familiars. Yeah
So yeah, you're covered. I love it. You got the whoo-hoo. Hey, did you know there's an owl in the room?
In your room
You're supposed to say who and then I'm supposed to say you well, I'm looking at it. I'm looking at the owl right now
I know I said, hey, did you know there's an owl in the room?
That was a stupid, don't ever let me do that again.
All right.
Okay, cool.
Um, I didn't go get my phone charger.
I got a, my God.
Oh, my you.
I hope everyone's not bored.
No, there's, you got 30 people in here.
Um, we have 30 people in here they're not here for me. Um, I come here for no, I'm just kidding
You're all you just always been a fave. Just one second. My daughter stole my phone charger
So I've go to the other end of the house and momentum
Okay, thank you for your patience
You were gonna like talk to somebody and they're not fully awake and they're delirious
My daughter was okay. I need my phone charger. She's like rises up like from the dead. She's like
What do you want to do with it? I was like clearly charge my
I need to tie somebody up with it. I'll be right back. You literally just asked me about a million Mason questions about one thing
It's like a relax. Um
Just a moment. We got shami that wanted one. Okay. I'm gonna grab my
animal oracle deck because it's og
You're welcome psych. We're just taking over the entertainment
Psych will be up in about an hour. Oh, I know like 20 minutes. Yeah, he doesn't sleep long
He wakes up to pee and then he sees the chat is like empty. He just shuts it down
Aw, well frick, I hope everybody's been good.
Okay, just every time I've popped on in the last while,
even though I haven't been around,
oh, I just tricked myself.
This is the wrong dick in the wrong box.
Anyways, he's just, you know, it's hard to watch
and you guys can come at me, I don't care.
It's hard to watch your YouTube family fight with each other.
Like, especially when it's like the,
kind of the OGs of like the what do you call it like the matriarchs or the patriarchs of the family like the glue to in between you know and like everything's just kind of been an unadhesive incoherent fucking like hurtful disaster and you don't know where to kind of insert yourself to even kind of make a difference you know and I've been gone for a while it's rough for you especially
I want to fix everything, but I need a little bit.
You can't. You can't fix it. You have to just let them do it.
No, that's another thing. Just say fuck it and let them cook, you know?
That's what I do, because everybody else is trying to fix it. There's no fixing it.
No, because then you just kind of throw yourself into the fire, no matter what you do, it's
not going to be effective in the sense of what you would like it to with your implication
of it.
You know what I mean?
Exactly.
And you're only hurting yourself because then you're going to be dragged into it and then
you're going to be torn apart by everybody just going at you.
Fucking friend or whatever it is like it's you you suck if you stick up
You don't you don't have to be you don't have to be a shit friend
You just can support each of them separately and just say look I'm not gonna get in the middle of it
Well, that's where I've kind of always made like a standard basis of how I roll in general like I mean
I'm not gonna fuck with the drama. I'm also not gonna like
Hang around and watch her winter each other like shit. I'll pop in if it's you know
And it's not like I'm like oh
I'm avoiding the drama because you've all seen me lose my mother fucking shit
But I have to really have my had my fill
where and then it's like watching people
and ties each other and everybody's kind of doing the tip for tat thing and I was just like you know
what I'm gonna let it settle um because I don't have enough sage then then there's people that try
to bring you in they try to pull you into the whole mix oh then you're okay did it pick a side
pages that beat us right now or pages I'm never gonna pick a fucking side and I'm always gonna stick
So like that's the thing and that's where I stand and I always have made that quite clear
since I've been a part of this community.
And I feel like I guess if you establish that and people know what to expect from you then that's that you know
That's it. Your friends won't ask you to choose. That's that's the way it is and we shouldn't have to that's the thing
Someone's beeping with somebody. I would if you ask me
It's like, you know divine can't intervene unless you like give permission to intervene with your free will choices and your life, right?
So it's kind of like the same thing if you think about it with friends and with other energies or people in your life or things, right?
Yeah, man
Just gotta be calm with everybody. That's the way I do it
I mean like you're just talking shit. I'm gonna be like, hey, that wasn't very nice
And I know you know better, but like i'm not gonna sit there and be like, oh, you're just
Yeah, I don't judge anybody
I don't have to like everything that people do, to like them, you know, because I know I'm the same way.
I don't ask people to love me for everything I do. I mean, they can.
I don't even love me for everything I do. I don't expect anyone else to, but it's cool if you do.
Yeah, I know what you mean. I'm smoking what you're rolling.
People love the drama, man. People live for it.
It is what you make home is where you make it. Yeah
Yeah
It is what it is. I don't know that that's the stupidest t-shirt cliche thing to say
But like it is it is what it fucking is it is what you make it and it is what you allow it, right?
It's all on you
We're here for good times who comes who wants to go to a place with that miserable all the time doesn't make any sense
Um, I have like a double fucking maybe quadruple like not double spaced page of names that probably
Okay, so what we're gonna do here is cuz every
This is gonna I don't even like how this is gonna come out my mouth. I know Jamie. I didn't yet just one second
Okay
Can you get your memories back? Yeah you can. I will teach you how. It's hard to explain on here.
I could do my best, but I would prefer to like discuss it with you or like work with you
in a session or like a personal level. Like we did other big
strange things like that. You know what I mean? Because it's like an intimate to yourself
and spirit and your energy kind of thing.
Because I am gonna
Goddy nice spelling error
What you can't write the other one, can you I don't know I I don't know I
Do all these things like this
Yeah, Ray, like, you know that some of us are, like, definite 90s when we, like, put, like, a fucking money sign instead, where it does not even appropriate so that the spelling is really an ass sign.
I'm shadow banned for half the shit I say, so I have to write shit like that.
Look it, look it, that's what's up.
He wrote it.
Yeah, see, he can write it, but I can't write it.
Let me see, let me see if I can write it.
Whoops. Oh
There we go. Is it there?
No, see it says it why no, no, I wrote it after that I corrected after that it's not there
It doesn't let me do it
YouTube's on my ass even on my ass for years
You're just, you're the only person who's like,
you're not allowed to say that fucking word.
Paige, you have no idea what YouTube's done
to me over the years.
Believe me.
YouTube has destroyed the best parts of me.
I've been persecuted for a long time.
Forever we shall be.
Billy can attest to that.
I got a witness, got a lot, I got witnesses.
Well, there he is, this camera.
Okay, Shem. I'm gonna do the, um, what the fuck are they called? Oh, the Astrology Astrology.
I don't know why I tried to make that word. It's like when Joe Dirt was like, just deer,
there's deer-tay. Can't judge that. Okay, um, Astrology Reading Cards. So these are the
ones with the Planet Cards, the Zodiac, and the House. I'm gonna pull one of each for
What is it moonology manifestation or manifestor? I don't know. I don't know. Oh
The manifestation moonology oracle cards. I literally said it just in the wrong order. You're welcome
Welcome back page. Okay. Here we are
Everything is coming. I hope so the world needs to be recockied in a good way
Those all right
Okay, so for the house card we have the seventh house coming out
So just a minute before I start like the full reading. I do want to do what I do normally
All right
It's so funny your name is shamrock and I do see it's like a four leaf one. So like there's like four
options or four doors so
and all of them bring prosperity and luck,
doesn't matter which one you go through,
I feel like two of them are causing,
wow, let's be real.
I think three of them are causing you
like this mental anguish in a way that you're like,
God, why is it bothering me so much?
It's so annoying.
Like if you brush your teeth and you're like,
fucking, keep circulating.
So I don't know why the universe is doing that to you.
But it's a lesson that you have to learn right now and yes, they're all going to be great
Like no matter what you do its success, but I feel like it's just to light a fire up under your ass for something
Does that make sense? It's like you just need a little bit of a push. It's like spirits like I got your back
I'm not gonna
Push you I promise and then they got like their fingers crossed behind their back and push you into the pool anyways
Like a step like a I don't know like it like a brother or sister would just to be like oh my god
Like I actually really liked being underwater
So I think it's like something out of your comfort zone is what I want to say if there's something that is like
Um, maybe it's like something long-term. I feel like and it's also something to do with maybe like your name
I don't know significant partners or like
Business like something long fucking term like you have to dedicate yourself to this. Okay, so
Anyways, let's do the planet card
Oh yeah, so Seventh House is like, it's,
this area of your life is like romantic business,
family, anything with like a significant kind of
partnership or longevity or long-term focus.
I don't know if it makes sound effects for everything,
I'm not very professional.
I'm not professional, I'm Paige.
So the fact that these are like being sticky is what I call it and no matter what way I
try to see the shuffle to get the jump card or the message card, it is not giving me one.
So are you stuck in thought about something like there's a thought process you're waiting
Stagnant in an answer if you're like fuck. I'm sick of waiting for my language, but
Yeah, this is crazy. Just a minute. Let me do the zodiac and see if it'll hold
Let's switch it up. Oh, that's where there it is right there. Let's switch it up. It's time to switch it up punch
I think that that's your go-ahead to be like, hey
It's time to switch it up a little bit
So let's see
Okay, and it's gonna be a little bit tricky at the beginning and that's okay, but eventually it's going to flip look at that
Oh lovely, so we have it torus
So this is all about you know in tarot its pentacles and abundance and slow going but very much worth all of the
effort or the
energy that you're going to
To exude or put into it is always going to be a great outcome. So like the energy around you shows the abundance of nature
It's rich earthy productive yet relaxed and slow
You know, so just just be patient with yourself. I know that you're feeling an urgency behind some sort of oh
To see and then to come out. That's insane. Okay
We have Mars coming out so your physical energy drives strength and fighting spirit
But it was in the reverse. So that's what I was just saying. You're I love when spirit does that
Your energy and your drive
It's not kind of behind any
Any specific thing right at this time. It's like I know all the doors that I can open
I know I have options. It's not about picking the right one
It's almost like you're wanting the right one to pick you
That's a fucked up thing to say, but I do feel like that's the energy you're in now Neptune coming out is what your fantasies?
yearnings longings and potential
for illusion
Are you you want something more for yourself?
Um, but you are such an abundant person because you put so much behind everything that you
do and take so much pride in everything that you do, um, and you have a lot of control.
a lot of self-control, is that you're just trying to ease up on that a little bit maybe
because you become a little bit OCD within others' lives as well, so it's caused you
stress.
There's something about wanting to kind of like, slay some dragons and make reality out
of some of these fantasies or see if you can do so.
It's maybe a challenge for yourself in a good way though.
Okay, let's do this.
We're going to do, are you, everyone's still there?
Sorry, I just totally don't know what I want to do this.
I have to, but.
Oh, geez, honey, okay.
Okay, we're gonna tap into some taro.
Yeah, there's just some inner self.
You just, you're doing so much on the inside,
but I feel like, do you feel like an imprisonment sometimes
where it's like, okay.
You're like me and the aspect of I'm super tough. I'm gonna go through this. I'm gonna go through it by myself
I'm going to
Hello
Ghost
I'm gonna go through this myself. I I don't know if it's
Something I should talk about to other people. I don't want to bother other people. I'm strong enough to do this
But sometimes we do need help now. We have the Queen of Swords coming out and so it's like okay. You're very very much
You ready to cut any motherfucker off
Immediately you're like I don't play games
I earned this throne because I have thought every single thing out to the last detail
Not only for myself, but others as well as outcomes on the inside and the outside in thought
And you know her hand is above the clouds her head's above the clouds and that sword is above the clouds
So her head is she is just
It's an I know what I need for myself and I know
How it can affect others and what my kind of like what your greater
Like you're what your your purpose is purpose. That's what it is. I know my worth. I know my purpose
But do other people know that and that maybe is a question that you have sometimes where then it kind of gives you that
weird back cycle of hey
I don't know if I'm not great at that because it was a discouragement leads to discernment of oneself
Yeah, and then okay
so
Yeah, we've got like that's kind of wands carrying some burdens carrying some burdens. Are you carrying your burdens?
Are you carrying other people's?
Well as an empath you obviously collect others, but
Okay, then we have the page of wands coming out and we have a chunk here. We also have
The aid of cups so you have definitely been
very much more optimistic in the past, which kind of had recently led you to bad taste in your mouth with some experience.
And you're like, fuck these cups. Emotions mean nothing to me at this point. I kind of feel like I'm empty.
Because I had big dreams and some buddy or something crushed them.
Ooh, the lovers.
The love thing you have for yourself, I feel like you need to nourish that more or as much as like maybe we could work together like I feel like
the loss of the other half of your heart
kind of
Kind of I don't know. I feel like sometimes you're at this precipice where it's like, okay, I want to
Maybe put myself out there
But fuck that, you know, it's like this withdrawn. It's like one foot out and then oh, I don't I don't like the chilly air or you know like
Yeah, we I've let it in the cold this car seriously
That's crazy
Your it feels like every time you try to put yourself out there since and in the matters of the harder emotions
You've been left out in the cold
But the Sun the Sun coming out. That's beautiful the Sun coming out
Get it you gotta you gotta
Let go of the past experiences even as of like, you know your most recent hurt because as we throw them in the garbage
We make room for
New things to come in. It's like cleaning out your closet. You know what I mean or like your attic just clean constantly be dusting your fucking cells
You know what I mean?
Clean your attic. It's not full of like old doll shoes and like Christmas lights and stuff
cobwebs
You know, there shouldn't be a storage area for hurt. There just shouldn't be. Yeah
But you're coming out of this decision mode. You're sick of juggling. You do see the clear
path on both sides and you would like to sit in an emperor energy
Both open a dick about it. You know what I mean? You just you know
Know what you want. Why am I echoing?
Got it. How do I fix it?
Is it me?
No, it's me.
No, listen, I think my whole shit rebooted. So hold on. Go ahead. Go ahead. Sorry
No, it's okay
Okay, so the tarot is done. I'm gonna take the moonology cards. Hopefully you're still here with me sham
I just feel like I was muted the whole time, but I know I wasn't
Let's move this
Well, it makes sense that that's being affected though because I do feel like you're you're comfortable in most areas of your life
But there is the matters of the heart, right?
Well, I hope you about it hopes the psych doesn't mind him. I mean, I know he doesn't because you don't
It's very game if you fall asleep, but
Reading on his channel and not trying to promote myself
okay one more shuffle okay i think it's fixed yes it is oh geez you must be god or something
oh i don't even know just your actions okay so
i'm frozen on the panel
What is the number of three have anything to, is that significant to you, Shammi?
So also we have Gemini, Libra, more Gemini.
Oh, I guess with this we also have, we have earth, earth, fire, and air.
We have water.
Okay, so we do have all of the elements.
But it's not balanced, and that's okay. So we have the new moon in Gemini think it through make sure that whatever you're doing at this time
master manifestor that
you
Strategically
Sift through these these these options these thoughts these offerings whatever they may be that you're trying to
trying to
Base the next two years of your life on really is they're giving me that timeframe of maybe two years like this is a dedication that you have to be certain about.
And there's mountains, but there's lots of light, you know what I mean?
So first quarter moon in Libra, keep your heart open.
Oh, you shithead. Hey, if someone's interested, let me just cut to the chase. If someone's interested in you,
I know that I know what you've you've been through. I see your heart. I see your soul.
I mean, you know, I've been connected long enough. I know your energy. You know what? You are ready.
You are deserving as much as you are open to it, right? And three is your number.
Just make sure you don't have got three bitches and if you want three bitches, make sure they don't know each other.
I'm just kidding trying to make you laugh sham. Okay, but just just make sure that you know
You're not selling yourself short or you know missing out on things because of your fears or
your you what you're holding on to those bags of
of
What do you want to I mean it's kind of not expired love, but
No longer available love
There's a certain amount that's healthy to keep but the rest is just
It's just darkness and dead weight, okay, and
Hard to move forward when you're carrying all that baggage and you ain't looking you're gonna trip and stumble quite a bit
Okay, or you're not gonna see things that are right in front of you
So the first quarter moon in Gemini now speak your world into being you decide what you want
You are the master manifester. We create what we speak we manifest our thoughts and we project and attract what we feel
So you have all the power magic wand anyways. Love you
Be fucking confident about it, too. Okay, you got this. Don't be skirt. We don't skirt around here
I was finding a new community
Yeah, okay
Is everybody gone what happened is it over
I don't know. It can be. Yeah. I don't know. I don't know. I think you were doing a reading. So I didn't want interrupt
Yeah, no, that's okay. Thank you for the good. Thank you for the respect. Yeah
Okay, Sam Rockstone, okay, cool. I hope that that was like I hope that that resonated
I was watching little Martin Lawrence while you were doing the reading.
Jamie, why are you saying no honey? What's going on?
Okay, Jamie, do you want me to quick reading too?
Because I feel like you absolutely do.
Let's do this.
We're gonna do it the same way we just did Shammy's, um, except for... let me move this around.
Ooh, I don't know if I want to. I think that I want to use a different deck to start. Just a moment. Just a moment.
Okay, Jamie, we're going to do the tail oracle, like tail zen oracle, to start your reading.
Well, actually my mouth is going to start your reading, but all right, my dear.
Let me tap into you. That sounds so weird.
Did the tow truck steal from you right off the get-go? I can see that there was some things that were misplaced and or not documented
I
Don't want to call it theft. Maybe it was an accident, but at the same time I don't I also do
Feel that there might be some shady business going on, but I feel like it's from
It's tied to the report from the police. Does that make sense to try to make sense of that report or to back it in some way or another?
I do feel like there is some some gray area for sure that you should look into.
Okay, you're welcome.
Um, I think obviously, um, I would look into them working together. Yeah, like to cover, you know what I mean, because if you think about it, the affiliates, and you could probably even ask, you know, anybody in authority or in, it's like our community in that community or that group, right?
Or it's like, okay, the police said this, and so they're, you know,
Net I don't know what you call it tighten it. Yeah, exactly. You thought so you know what I'm trying to say you're smoking when I'm rolling
Thank you for saving this feel
Okay, so I'm gonna pull one of these
Hey Graham, what's up? Okay
Okay, so my cards
Are just I don't know how I explain it be chunky and slice so sliding and chunk. Okay, so being
Confidently sneaky is what I'm getting from this
Yeah, your truck needs to probably sacrifice no, I'm just kidding honey. I'm just trying to make you laugh
Oh, no after that shit happened
And I seen the video like the pictures and stuff were sent to me and it affected me in the way that it did
I feel like anything
To do with this case of your vehicle and like your oxidant is it's gonna be
It's just gonna be fucked up. It's just gonna I don't know how else to put that like I can't put it like it's gonna
Make the roadies is back
your body you know what's weird on my TV you have the owl avatar with the halloween shit but on my device is the ghost
yeah I know I just saw that too I was frozen for about 10 minutes
pretty cool
super chat goes thank you so much
Oh
Who woke you up ghost
Just I heard I heard my boy. I heard my mind. Keep go go on panel wake up. You go sleep
Up what up come on in ghost
Thank you
Jamie, so we have work on what has been spoiled, so healing and correct past mistakes, make
repairs, clean up corruption, restore balance, and take some responsible action upon all
of this.
And the number 18 is significant, as well as the color green or teal.
Contemplation, you know gaining overview. It's a very dark card. It's not dark in the sense of ominous, but it's very much
The teal with the black so it's it's coming from
coming from a place of necessary cleanup in order to face some of these things, you know,
detached observation and an increased understanding
in the time of this, solitude,
integration through reflection will
greater cause, like it's all about the greater cause for you, for your insides, for your mind, for your mental stability,
and then we have 38 with opposition.
for you I feel like this is the people that you're dealing with but not only that it's causing
this situation is causing you to be um like opposition for yourself your own ops right
okay we're going to do one more oh so small
Small is beautiful. So find the extraordinary in the ordinary. Keep it simple, use discretion,
slow down, tend to the details, and pay attention. So when I see all this together,
it's like you're not wrong, listen to your intuition, and I also want you to like the
smallest, finest detail will be what will
Oh, um, how do I say be your glory or your victory in this endeavor like hundred percent?
So I'll pull three tarot and then one moonology. Okay?
So just pay attention to the little details don't make sure that's what's being skipped right now is other people overlooking those small fine details, too
It's kind of like a
Same fucking situation. Okay justice justice coming out sideways. So there is
Justice is going to be yours. It's just going to take you looking into these fine details for you to put it into action
So that that's the outcome, right?
Okay, just we've got
Okay
So we've got the three of wands. You're kind of just sitting there. You're looking out. You're thinking you're like, okay
This what what's in the future? What what am I waiting on? What can I do to stop waiting on it?
Where are the answers? Right? You're just in limbo a little bit of limbo, but lots of
Intuitive direction and like certainty. Does that make sense? What a weird way to say something
Pardon me, ooh
Okay, and then we have the queen that we have the queen of ones. There's lots of passion
There's lots of drive when it comes to this and there's lots of you like I want to find the answers
I want to make it better. I want to fix it. I know I'm not wrong and like you listen into yourself and like
That's where you get into that that throne of certainty when it comes to okay. I'm gonna follow my passion
What my guts telling me and my I'm gonna use every ounce of drive when it comes to that fire, right?
Now let's have one of these to come please
Please oh alright, so we have
Sajji more fire coming out new moon and Sagittarius so focus on the positive Jamie keep your mind in and not a dark space
Okay, because we have the new moon and cancer you have to relax
Or else you're gonna keep yourself in this dark state and like be proud of yourself for listening to your intuition because
You're gonna be even more proud of yourself when the outcome is to be okay
Yeah, anyways, hun. I love you. There you go. Oh
That was sweet
And that was that was beautiful. That was beautiful. Yeah, I agree ghost
Well, thanks fellas, aren't you aren't you swell?
We need some positive energy around here lately
I'll switch it up for you ghost. Yep, and I'll see it
Yep, it's still ghost over. It is. That's right. It's spoo tober
Those only work if you have the light so we can see the shadow shadow puppet, right?
Well, he's no gang signs on the panel, so I please
Have you guys heard of puppetry of the penis there actually is a Broadway show. Yeah, it's gross
I've never seen it, but like I'm not surprised that it is a thing
Wait repeat what you just said
Origami
President of like Ukraine once play like a
Blanket penis. Let me blanket piano with his penis on a comedy show
Well, I depends to you as that's debatable
How do we go from a beautiful reading to you you you were gummy cocks and
Alex what are you doing for tomorrow brother? You're gonna have a good day tomorrow for tomorrow
Yeah, what are you doing tomorrow?
October 20th, or 17th, I don't know if you guys can see.
It's October, we're going to be talking October.
You're going to have a good day tomorrow?
Why is there no labs today or something?
I'm going to need labs for tomorrow.
All day, labs.
I'll be lurking in the background.
You guys talk.
Look what you did, Paige.
You ran him away.
Who's playing the piano?
I like the piano, man.
Well, guess what I could just I'll just go I'll just you myself. I'll just go to myself
I'll just let's pull us like I'll be in the back
Finally
Jesus God
Stop talking
We're waiting for a fucking cocktail I'm table dancing with Paige right now waitress
Your table dancing I'm watching laughing I'm pretending I don't
Well, I'm table dancing with ghosts and I'll just be throwing lobster. Hey, hey, brother. Hey
Let's go. So don't start. All right. You're okay. I liked that. That was very Canadian. Hey
And you're squeezing ghosts his cheeks, but like
What what's what's sub-it cheeks are you squeezing sir? It's by the squeezing of pancake
It's funny you can sit about cheeks and lips say
Don't be rude to her we're not talking about her ass don't say pancake
Fucking rude
Bannock but because I'm native and you gotta see her feet though the bottom of her feet man. What but
Bannock but
It's fry bread like it's like my hair it's like my culture's fucking thing other than dried meats your ass is like rye bread
No, like it's like case. It's a joke. It's an it's
Hey, right
Fresh fried bannock with butter
Fresh fried bannock, it's a fish then
with those little black teeth
that I did not churn because I'm not a huderate
I'm native and
with strawberry banana jam that I made
ohhh strawberry banana jam
made of what?
made of european
holy shit page
strawberry banana
what? how many?
strawberry banana jam
No, there was another one. Yeah, it's too Canadian for New York. You can't even
Pancakes with some butter are nice any fucking thing with butter in that jam is probably meant
Anything's better than like I'm like they put baked beans like
There's fucking elevator music in the background
Okay, first
I hope we make it through this panel
No, I'll put you on a 10 second time out
You didn't even notice
He's like just kidding
Oh, he doesn't have a surprise
That was the waitest unsurprise I ever seen
Look like he's up to something
You look like a mystery you look like a lobster face girl. I don't I look cute
You look like you look like a praying mantis. I'll be honest with you. I'm not trying to be
That could be a good thing or a bad thing. It's debatable. You guys remember when Bita called Psycho Praying Mantis when he was like posing in his
Do you want me to not have that picture up?
I'm a fan of it
the
Oh, I do know him
He looks like
mascot of Burger King
By the way, you can get that you all you have to do is ask when you go to burglars
You're supposed to give it to you for free. I'm gonna crash out. This is what psyche was looking like just like burger peasant
That was rude
This guy you'll fuck up your day
burger don't
You should have put like you should have like edited it and put like red glasses on it and got rid of it
I want to wafer, bro
Then he would look like a crazy kindergarten teacher that drives a punch buggy that matches her glasses
The face tattoos. Well now it kind of looks like a teacher to be honest with you. Do they have Burger King in Canada?
I hope so great Gallagher bear not teach my kids
And they definitely have another border and they're definitely living eats Burger King for sure
Oh, it's gold. Look. We have Burger King. We have McDonald's. It's gold before you gain that on your pounds.
That was me. Yeah, before I gained 100 pounds. Why are my eyes so close together?
That's jazz bono.
That's I see that people that's a little kid that says I see
Was that movie cold it's called the sixth sense man. Yeah, that shit. That's it. That's a little kid
Yeah, what other movie did you what he had the Omen I think no that wasn't even him
No, that's Wade well, yeah, he was yeah, he was he was older. Yeah, he was uh, I do know what you're talking about. Yeah
Thank you. He was and he also played a different one. He's like a long legs. I think he's like the love interest, whatever
Staying glass human portrait. Oh, he's making a song that's a surprise. This is me. This is my face in red
That's U. F. A. to you girls with pussy out.
Yeah, it was a bloody Sunday, it was.
She had her break down.
That's U. F. A. to you girls pussy on her period.
Nothing wrong with it.
That's me.
That's your queen.
I don't fucking love her.
It was the best night ever.
Yo, I fucked up my girl on her period once it looks like a murder scene. I swear to God
Bad was covered and blood I was covered from head to toe
It looked like I was stabbing the beast of death stabbed about 67 times
Yeah, it was just good fucking though. Yo, it looks like I should wrap your face in the sanitary napkin and put you
I need a little moist towel
You know what I'm talking about?
Watch on the screen.
I was about to write that out.
Imagine getting fucked up like this.
I would rather get stabbed repeatedly in my ovaries and everywhere else in my face
like that's
That's the outcome
What bad day wait what I miss what I miss you whether you're stabbed in your ovaries over where you don't get to see or here
We're gonna make it a mystery just like your face. Thank God because I don't want to know what that's it
Well, you guys where did that come from anyway? Who started that conversation?
What?
Jesus
Let's keep it clean. Okay. Oh, I'm here. I'm gonna move on
Listen, man
My man, please tell me
Yeah, I love it
Call it Le Grandi Papa
No, that's how you like it, huh? You like it on the papa. You like it on the cracker Papa
I do not like like around a Papa. I
Can't believe you in love with me. I like lay average Papa
Can't believe you in love with me. I guess I'm out
Ghosts, did you hear page one?
At a certain point I stopped kind of listening like once you guys are like
Tyropractive
Anyways ghost would you like card? I don't know. I don't wanna fucking guard
No, it wouldn't make me feel better. I just thought that that maybe that's what
That's he got that's just
That's why I gave money I wanted a tarot read
Baby just bread
Not because you're being
And like you want one though. You really want one
Just one though
Was that the surprise
He was gonna play a song for you
Yeah
All right, he left again read him a card
Ghost part-time do all of us have a song at this point. I think ghost you have a song, right?
You're ready to crash out when the moment feels right
I'd like that moment
You light up the night
For the night
With that wild grin
Every time you're rolling
If the fun begins
Thank you, ghost
I won't forget you
You make me laugh till my face turns blue
This is gonna surprise, though
There's an old tool
Are you gonna jerk off to it on me?
Maybe.
You can't shut up like it's bad.
What the fuck are you doing?
No, no, no.
What the fuck?
I'm gonna rub one out.
That's not for you to know ever.
It's just for me to think about it.
Alex, give me your hand!
When you're quiet, I'm talking a page about important stuff here. Why is it you slain?
What's up?
We can't see your feet.
You can see these toes.
You alright?
Yeah.
I know what the hell I'm talking about.
Because it's my song, babe. It's our song, baby. Jesus.
What do you look like?
I have golfing calves.
No, let's break you.
I knew it, babe. You think.
She don't fake. She don't play games. She's the calm in the storm
Beautiful the spark in the
Prairie page your pure gore
She's a real one
Love on stage
That's the legend
They call
Oh, it's got to hurt!
Love it!
You know I'd say I'll brush my teeth to that. That's not that was nice
Oh, he's muted you load his mic
You might bill you might you got to hit the speaker button we can't hear you William
William
Can you hear me now?
Yeah, yeah. Yes, sir. We can
Over and out
All right. I was
I was up. I was just on will I was just about will Durant's panel
So he's he fucked with it, and then he put me back stage. Oh, that's it again. He's mad
He's he's well, you know, I'm doing what I got to do got he
Now it is so I come here to tear everybody up high psych
I
Yeah, you left
Yeah, he left to cry because he didn't like the party
And are you crazy bastard?
Just chill man, enjoy
How you doing psych
I woke up about maybe half hour or so ago and just to sayings that but I had a good time yesterday morning
Gotti, you missed it. What I miss
It
Yeah, you up on my panel yesterday morning. Oh, wow what an exciting day
You missed that was very exciting. I'm glad
Rage rage quit nothing. I see if Charlie will be exciting
Well, I got on about his brother living with him. He's fucking his brother. Yeah, it's what yeah
Yeah, and now and now and now their little friend Wiggins. Yeah, some guy, uh, Arthur
Boekross
Right, he's saying that that's my real father that Robert Hayden isn't my dad and my nephew
Came up on my panel and and we went up on Wiggins panel. Yeah, you missed it
That name is funny Wiggins
Somebody
I died somebody
Wiggins wake us tomorrow
That's me that did that you you did that, right?
My chat is open if anybody in psych knows he's welcome. God. Do you owe me a favor? That's why I come here
When you get around
What now
It's a troll Wigan and will Durant night since they want to fucking play fuck darts
Support others aren't we?
No, yeah, I didn't come here to cause trouble. I come here to
To what
So, I'm going to get my stuff right out my chest.
Tell them about the photo you showed.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Don't tell them.
I'm not reading what you told me.
Don't tell them that.
What photo did you show?
Do you need a photo?
Who shows this photo?
Don't tell them.
Nothing, psych.
Look who's here
Who's fucking Mike is doing that
Stop baby boy. Yeah, you're the happiest man in the planet
So I can you please let that cat go. We gotta clear something up. We can we clear something up with Joe?
Johnny get yourself up here, please. We got a clear
Whatever you think it was me it wasn't me
he's a good guy, he is a good guy, he will tell the truth, if he wants to say fuck you to whoever he'll say it, and it won't tell the truth
what does he think I said, I don't even know what she thinks I did
I think he's saying he wants to tell her something that sounded like you, because you know what people would sound like you a little bit sometimes
okay, let's say they sounded like me, what was the name of the person, if it wasn't you
Tony, he sounded like you
Disrespectful to you, but I don't have behind the other name. Maybe if we all put the fuck
All right, all right, here she is. Let's clear this up
Yes, what do you got to say, Johnny? What do you have to say? I have nothing to say
I don't know what you're even talking about. It's like gave me filled me in a little bit
But you got something up your ass that it's about me. I don't know what it is
You know what it is. I have no idea what it is. You swear
Sweet on myself. I don't think it was him. I think it was someone down and like him a little bit. Yeah. Well, what is this?
What what are you implying that another show on another show and the right you can tell where?
It was memory you're at
You remember you were asking me about those other shows my opinion. I was asking you
Yeah, about a week or two ago. You're asking me what I thought or about these three other show. Oh, yeah
Yeah, but your um, it's me. You're good psyche buddy Tam it and then the other one
Right and you said to me, what do you think would be like the best fit and we were talking about it remember?
I think so. Yeah, and then then somebody cut made of it
And you know, maybe I'm wrong
It just sounded like you and it was like bad timing and it was on on one of the streams and it was
pretty uh it was it was just like it i think i could probably have like a personal conversation
like a hold on ghost it's almost done ghost it's almost done it's almost done the only
who gives a fuck we don't know about it release the only place i've gone joni was uh buddy i've
only been on the buddy's panel that's the only one i've been on so if it's if it's anywhere else
it wasn't me
I had a climb of steps just to get on this fucking
To get on this and no
If it wasn't I'd be like so thankful because didn't you didn't feel the cool breeze for me in the last couple
Yeah, that was me not speaking cuz I was like shit man that motherfucker
You went up and like torched me and they all believed it and I thought no that it's not a real serious
Johnny, I don't know you well enough to torch you. Okay, good
Well, yeah, but I didn't know you promise on your penis. I promise on everything
All right, let's I'm unshackling. What was the name? Well name of what the stream no the person
I don't I didn't even catch the name
It was a New York accent
Yeah, definitely wasn't me definitely was he said like somebody said I
Struck a channel because I had so many trolls that they were trolling
So I said I'm reporting you to about the troll but I didn't but I just said it that everybody turned on me
And then the caller came in and yeah, she's a she's a strikeaholic
who's panel i don't really want to say it a lot you don't even know the third one out that's out
of the three that yeah i've never been there i've never been there i've never been to his panel
Well, I unscribed unsubscribed and never went back that day, but uh, yeah, I'm so glad to hear that because it was like kind of bizarre
And it sounded I played it for psych. It's like, is this him?
And he goes, I don't think so, but it sounds like him a little bit, but it's weird that you guys can't even decide for my voice like that
That's that's right. Yeah
Me I did it. What's your problem with it? You have no idea
No, I'm gonna run one that you have a problem like why I
Problem first, okay, so what's your problem then? I don't know
Now with you see we had I got other problems. We're good Johnny good
So much shade your way apology accepted. I saw you up on buddies the other night. We are in a good old time
Yeah, you didn't throw much my way. It was just the cold shoulder. Oh, I cold I iced you
I ramble on but like
I'm kind of I'm becoming the stoic queen. It only it only bothered me because I don't know why I'm like, what the fuck
You go, that's not my joke. You go. That's not my jony. What's up? Yeah, I don't know what happened
Yeah, that's what I mean. I'm tony. I actually did strike your channel. You did. Oh all along. Yeah, it was me
What you don't know you don't you have no problem with that. You don't argue about that or nothing
And that's how you handle problems everybody yeah, and there it is
And then we'll call you down when you don't know what the fuck you're talking about yeah
I'm talking to you J
What's up, darling you don't talk about yourself at all you just accuse this man
Goes he wants to run it is it just people with the name ghost there are such fuckheads pretty much
Why don't you just start getting, like, anti-semitic that I'll know it, like, goes with the flow?
Anti-semitic, you don't know what semantics mean.
I'll get good and clean semantics.
Call me a Jew.
Quick, before you go.
What do you mean Sasha? You don't want to talk to me?
Hey, we got Hebrew hammer up here calm down. Oh my god. Wait, we're gonna juice
No
Hey, just a Nazi cat
I do wait what'd you say page?
Have a cat that I named tuxedo a little kitten. He looks like Adolf Hitler. Do you want to see?
It's okay, let me turn the oven off
Run around my house going fucking nine nine, okay
Nine nine like a horse
No, no in German. Oh, no. Oh, I was thinking nay nay
I only know one German in my personal life. He was a really good painter. Oh, no
Yeah, power doesn't count a power doesn't count
Brackets the oven
Bracken Z why chocolate chocolate? I think they be chocolate chocolate
Wait a second, I don't understand
You pop three boys. I need to talk for you gaudy, but I think she should apologize to you. She did twice
Okay
Oh
We handle these things like adults
Wait, we see the kitty cat
Here I have a picture of it. I got a KitKat bar. I found him like stop fucking choking that cat brother
Give me a break
KitKat Bar
Give me a piece of that KitKat Bar
Give me a break
I'm way more friendly than I am
Give me a piece of that KitKat Bar
Oh
Hello
What the fuck
Did he hit the camera?
Yeah
Was that Cinderella who the hell was that these people
Those page does a tuxedo
No, but who was holding it? Don't spin the Rella
You should have a little bit on the chin if you have a little goatee going
it does look like Hitler actually that's fucking funny
my cat looks like he was like looking over an inkwell and someone just went
dupe on his little head like no I'm just like
oh my god was that spend a rather a page they look so natural no makeup
Oh
All the blemishes were just hanging out
Blemish, that's how I like my woman. Just you know blemishes at all
No, that's around here. It's called a natural my journey. Oh my god
I
Sound like a whining
Joni the you live in your journey you gotta come and see the
New joysy she enjoys
Hey
That's fucking funny
No, I have a question for you
Do you remember what a block of flamingo
Gaggle of lonely ladies a gaggle. No, you guys have oh my god
Yeah, gaggle. That means like a gang. It's like a bunch color flamboyance
The plane the plane. I can't see anything help the plane the plane
Is into the chat
So we got a whitey you
What do you mean, go ahead?
Go ahead, I say.
I'm hammering Jews.
You go ahead.
I'm retarded, man.
Are you going to fix it?
I can't do it.
I don't know.
I don't think so. You don't get over it. Were you gonna cry about every fucking day. God, you come in like a fucking
The last time me and you started uh, we got bumped remember
That's why I thought it was no
I can't see nothing. She looks great. She put it in a little bit darker. It's in a ponytail you guys
Thank you, thank you steak. We love you too. I don't know where I love you guys
I love you too, but that was fucking random. Yeah, what's this shirt you got on?
You're like, oh, there ain't enough of a page for this shit.
There's none of sage for this shit.
Looks like one of Paige's paintings.
There you go.
None of sage for this.
Oh, it's a skull.
OK, I see it.
A skeleton hand-holding sage, see?
Yes.
I actually just saved Scythe, I just saved that on my Pinterest because I was going to use it as a background.
I sound like the drummer guy, don't I?
No, you do not sound like Mason.
Wait, Mason?
Hey, Mason.
Can you hear me?
Mason is like Captain Infinity of Questions.
Thank you, Paige.
I'm confused.
Thank you. So for the reading. Hi, Jamie's cowboys. Welcome, Jamie. How are you my girl? I love that hat. Oh
Thank you so much, but thank you
Who said that?
Jamie
Jamie just keep that bad
$30 stream
Anyone becomes a member today, I'll give you a 30 minute reading
on the phone privately if you'd like to become a member tonight. If you have five memberships,
I'll give you an hour reading twice. Joni, can you make me a member, please?
Why don't you just tell him you'll give him whatever he wants.
That works too.
Can we sing a song?
Can we play the page song again?
Can we play the brand new song?
Can we play it real quick?
She's like, no.
The one with the lips or her lips show like that?
Her lips are brand new guys.
Those lips are very sexy.
Listen for Alexander.
She's like, listen for Alexander.
she lines up a shot and swings smooth no range that's my canadian darling that's
prairie page
oh sexy that's prairie page
Baby
Gold and pay
Oh, they're pretty cool
There's a breeze through the evergreens
Alexander's heart's gone all the way lost
And that's mine, those prairie days
Yeah, she's a sweetheart
To the real I made
That's my Canadian bed
Just golfer's caps
My prairie pay
I heard Alexander
You can't even go
You can get in the pool from the Rockies to the lakes her laughter plays guitar too
She's the calm in the storm
When you're golfing wild in the rain tarot queen with that gentle grace you light up the coldest place
Yes, she's a real one
I want her to love me
That's the legend
They call
I can't see
That humming's like, fuck him with me.
Just here, guys, Kazooom is here.
Look at Kazooom.
Kazooom is here.
Hey, how's it going?
Good to see you.
How you doing, Kazooom?
Oh, that man.
Is that a man talking?
Kazooom.
Yes, it's Kazooom.
You got a fucking sucky hand.
Your voice is very sexy.
All right on, thanks.
Oh, right on, thanks.
He didn't say Kazooomers.
Wow, you didn't say Kazooomers.
He does voiceovers for famous shows.
He does cartoon characters too.
What do you actually sound like?
I'll be quiet.
This is what I sound like.
Okay.
It's like you just got wet.
It's really good.
Right on!
Just chilling around.
Okay, thank you. Salute.
And he's gay, guys!
All yours, pal.
Yeah, yeah, are you single is he your type and that voice is talking to that voice all night
I'll be close your eyes. Hey, he were hammered a shirt a picture though. I don't know
Is him are you Jewish? That's the question. No
I'm a pantheist
What the hell is that?
He said he's a pansy.
He's a pansy.
Are you guys panties?
He's panting shampoo.
Religious wise, I think the universe
is a giant living thing that we're a part of.
That's my belief.
Oh, like he's absolutely fucking about it.
Are we in meat suits?
That's what I want to know.
You have awoken whatever was inside of her.
Can you hear me?
Okay, testing one, two, three.
We heard you.
Don't get to hear me.
Johnny, we heard you.
Testy's one two. Oh you can hear me
No, I've said but we're in meat suits did you hear me
We're in meat suits all of us
Lady Gaga years ago wore a meat suit like steaks and stuff. Mine is like medium rare
definitely be rare great a fucking red Angus beef I think of that that band
Beatles album cover where they they had pieces of the ghost panel
What the hell with the link? Okay. I got a ghost back up here. Here we go. Is that ghost? The Arboretor?
I'll have what he's having.
He's the Arboretor, yeah.
Oh, well, shit.
He's the on-care Arboretor.
I won't forget you.
He's made of money, you know. Take it easy now. Now you can get a haircut.
Don't cut it too much now.
Hey guys, I love you all of all you guys. I've got to zoom. I got Hebrew hammer. I got
Yeah, you know, cute you bring hammers by the way. He's straight
We got Alex here he's straight wait someone told you I'm straight
I thought God I thought me and Goddy. I thought we went through this last time. Well, I detected detected. That was a lie
Guys, we have the Brady bunch going on right now
Very small to the left and none of the faces are moving when you talk what's wrong with this picture. I'm Marsha
The youngest one with curls, I don't know why they do that song.
Oh, it's the Brady Bones.
Oh, I'm sorry Steph.
And they knew they had to form a family.
There was one of ten of kids called a bunch of kids to the birth point of the kid.
Jimmy crack corn, and I don't care
I do care about that Jimmy crack corn
I don't care Jimmy crack corn, and I don't care
Remember when he was on the train with these hobos and then he was
I was in training day. They found the dog crack in some guy's mouth and they pulled it out
They killed him stuck in the middle with you
Allison trains what movie was that from?
Me
Drinking juice in the hood
Don't make me do it wait a minute
Do you remember the movie as good as it gets?
I know I'm so old, but that was like the boss.
And Jack Jigelson and the dog.
The dog.
Yeah, he was so funny.
How about when he was at the waitress and he sat down
and he goes, there's Jews at my table.
I'm sorry, I'm laughing.
I can laugh because I'm one of them.
But I remember that was the best movie.
I
can laugh because I'm one of them.
Okay, I love Jewish people.
I just wanted to tell people.
Jews are the best.
They are.
I love them.
Mazel Tov.
You know the dumb Jews.
How do you get a hundred Jews in a cab?
You throw a penny in it?
Something like that?
You know what I mean?
Who's that?
That's a good one.
I'm sorry, I'm trying to like grasp what's going on here. The last time I saw psyche on film, he was horizontal on a couch with a blanket over his head. And then, and then I talked to him privately. I swear to God, I saw my whole life story and I'm not kidding. This is a compliment in a weird way. All said it's like I stopped talking for a second and I heard that.
He was snort, like snort, but at first he got like mad,
but I feel like, I feel like a counselor, like a psychologist.
I sat there, I just started talking,
I looked up and heard little, she was naughty now,
kind of like President Trump, sorry,
if you're a Trump bursary, sorry, no offense.
But anyway, no, she was tolling naughty and I,
excuse me, ma'am, ma'am.
I had to like take a hammer and hit her knee
to see if a reflex is, but anyway, just joking.
No, but that means that...
I started singing you once I realized you were snoring I started singing like a lullaby to you
I like I had my way with you while you were sleeping. I totally went through you
Joni
Yeah, so Suvi, somebody else that I had there earlier, but I think she just smoked much
butter or something because I was talking her too and also I started hearing that rumbling
of that is her an earthquake somewhere help help and then I realized it went silent at the same
thing. I'm starting to get a little a little problem with me. What does that mean? Don't get
No way, it's not the whiny voice, it's one of them in a certain mode.
It means that people don't appreciate your content and it's a value.
I'm telling you now.
Vitamin B complex.
That's funny.
People in the camera have a picture of me.
It's like, it looks like the ghost Haley Joel Osmond picture,
but it's like aged.
And he's like, oh, this is a psyche.
And it has like my face a little bit.
Still offensive.
And he's like, oh, well, I don't want to offend you.
And then he puts it up again.
My god
It's really embarrassing
Are you taking photos of pages feet again?
Alex what he is and he's not showing them. That's the problem. I want to see her dirty souls. I maybe don't
Oh, no, I'm gonna have to confess. I'm gonna have to confess. I can't take it anymore. I can't take it, that's it.
There's an error with me, too.
I'm gonna have to confess.
Alex, you look like a liar.
God, we have to confess, Scott. Well, you don't, but I do.
I'm not confessing nothing. I didn't confess shit.
Wait.
I have to confess, like...
My feet don't belong in a church.
Fuck! Because it's such a good panel.
You know what, don't do it, don't do it, don't do it.
her name in the temples of night golden wings glowed in the candlelight
crowds came running just to see the flame but envy was the price of fame
and now he stands where the echoes fall with tarot in hand hearing every call
from praise to venom in the same breath said
burns gold, not red
Golden wings glowed in the candlelight
Crowds came running just to see the flame
But envy was the price of fame
And now he stands where the echoes fall
With tarot in hand hearing every call
From praise to ven-